<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_1">Crows, wipe the blood from the end of your claws\nSaid the vulture\nLets gather like storms for the war\nCrows, as the night turns its skin into coal\nDark as corpses but cluttered with gold\nThey will label you thieves, wolves, and whores\nBut you are nothing less than angels\nCast down and covered in black\n\nAin\'t this the bloodiest mess in the world? Said the virgin, a torn little girl\nBoy, you went and made a sweet wreck of my soul, and I\'ve already forgiven you\n\nAnd blood was running down\nHer dress in streams into her hands where she\nWas stitching on the flesh had left\nIn sections on the carpet near a bed that\nNever slept while she was sleeping\nIn her clothes that he had laid with on\nThe floor with all his fingers crossed\nIn hoping that that distance\nWouldn\'t grow\nBut how it grew\nAnd how it hurt\nAnd how it hallowed every memory had\nNever felt was threatened by a thing the world\nCould conjure up to kill them, but he let it kill them\nWhat a bunch of fools we lovers are\nAnd now shes smiling, with her self put back together\nJust a shadow of the past before the war\nAll sewn together, like a city sick from storms\nAnd sick of waiting for a god to call the floods out of her home\nWhat a bunch of fools we lovers are\nWhen tempted by the taste of flesh\n\n\"My boy, you are nothing more than a thief and a whore\nIn a suit of the finest of armor.\" laughed the vulture\n\"Pathetic little child, I am embarrassed for you.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_2">Pick up the phone\nBlessed be the thief, disguised in skin\nAnd blessed are the fingers that gesture him in\nPaint the receiver\nTo the side of the fake\nLying at the bottom of the staircase\nBroken elbows, and your coming through the window\n\nAnd whoever called night a blanket\nHad never the felt the cold\nAnd whoever called the night a blanket\nSo use your fingers, darling, and\nTear away at the restraints they call the body\nIt\'s the temporary things that rip us apart\nFor the body is but a piece of art for you to tear to pieces\n\nThis is history to thievery\nThese are only games we play\nHang up the phone</string>
</resources>