<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_1">Crows, wipe the blood from the end of your claws\nSaid the vulture\nLets gather like storms for the war\nCrows, as the night turns its skin into coal\nDark as corpses but cluttered with gold\nThey will label you thieves, wolves, and whores\nBut you are nothing less than angels\nCast down and covered in black\n\nAin\'t this the bloodiest mess in the world? Said the virgin, a torn little girl\nBoy, you went and made a sweet wreck of my soul, and I\'ve already forgiven you\n\nAnd blood was running down\nHer dress in streams into her hands where she\nWas stitching on the flesh had left\nIn sections on the carpet near a bed that\nNever slept while she was sleeping\nIn her clothes that he had laid with on\nThe floor with all his fingers crossed\nIn hoping that that distance\nWouldn\'t grow\nBut how it grew\nAnd how it hurt\nAnd how it hallowed every memory had\nNever felt was threatened by a thing the world\nCould conjure up to kill them, but he let it kill them\nWhat a bunch of fools we lovers are\nAnd now shes smiling, with her self put back together\nJust a shadow of the past before the war\nAll sewn together, like a city sick from storms\nAnd sick of waiting for a god to call the floods out of her home\nWhat a bunch of fools we lovers are\nWhen tempted by the taste of flesh\n\n\"My boy, you are nothing more than a thief and a whore\nIn a suit of the finest of armor.\" laughed the vulture\n\"Pathetic little child, I am embarrassed for you.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_2">Pick up the phone\nBlessed be the thief, disguised in skin\nAnd blessed are the fingers that gesture him in\nPaint the receiver\nTo the side of the fake\nLying at the bottom of the staircase\nBroken elbows, and your coming through the window\n\nAnd whoever called night a blanket\nHad never the felt the cold\nAnd whoever called the night a blanket\nSo use your fingers, darling, and\nTear away at the restraints they call the body\nIt\'s the temporary things that rip us apart\nFor the body is but a piece of art for you to tear to pieces\n\nThis is history to thievery\nThese are only games we play\nHang up the phone</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_3">I\'m reading over your shoulder\nIt says it in every line, in every curve and crack\nIt says it in every detail of your face\nUnmistakably apparent in this dull light\nTracing a separate letter, forming a separate word\nTwisting together to build the same beautiful sentence\nThe same painful realization\nThe cracks in your lips\nOpen with the books and\nThe smile shows the lines in your face\nPerfectly crooked, and perfectly familiar\n\nAnd for the moment, uncovered like a statue\nLay perfectly still. to show the cracks in your lips\nGive purpose to this pattern, and start to smile\nBurst into flames, disappear\nBefore your best intentions can no longer hide her ears\nFrom that which will make them bleed\nBefore your own two hands become too weak to hold the blood inside her wounds\nBefore reality explodes before you in a brilliant flash of spectral fires\nInto a thousand fragments of a past, long dead and gone\n\nThis is remembering the last time we touched\nThe last time we spoke\nWords ricocheting off empty tables\nVandalizing the pictures on these smoke-stained walls\nAnd i can feel your mouth as it opens from across the room\nYour tongue and lips forming the shape of your laughter\nIt\'s the curve of your stomach, its the bend in your legs\nIt\'s the remnants of the pages framed in the cracks of your bleeding lips\nIt\'s the curve of your stomach, it\'s the bend in your legs\nYour crooked teeth\n\nI\'m reading over your shoulder\nIt says it in every line, in every curve and crack\nThe same stupid message in every stupid bend and in every stupid stitch\nIn every inch of our peeling skin\nIt\'s tracing letters in the same sentence\nIt\'s screaming the same stupid thing\nLike the howling of a plane playing over and over and over and over and over</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_4">Oh, you\'ve a pretty mouth\nLeave your lips to linger on my skin and\nKiss me one last time\nI will roll off your tongue like a whisper in the winter\nSleeping in the sutures of the city\'s skin\nMake yourself remember me in cold and concrete\n\nWhen will you realize this city makes you real\nWhen will you realize your demons make you real\n\nOh, you\'ve a pretty mouth\nLeave your lips to linger on my skin and\nKiss me one last time\nI will roll off your tongue like a whisper in the winter\nSleeping in the sutures of the city\'s skin\nMake yourself remember me in cold and concrete\nIt\'s the way my hands felt lying still beneath your dress\n\nI am transparent\nI am a greenhouse filled with ghosts\n\nOh dear god, oh my god\n\nWhisper secrets, speak in a hushed voice\nThe first thing that you learn is that you never let them hear you\nIn a soundproof room, in a windowless world\nKeep your voice down or dull your words\nThen put on your bedroom face for him\nAll pursed lips and half-closed eyes with pink-stained skin\nScreaming for sleeping hands on downed dresses\nScreaming for dead legs come alive\nFor dead legs come alive\n\nOh dear god\nThere is no excuse for me</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_5">We move by instinct, darling\nLet our hands be hatchets\nLet us wander blindly, swinging madly \nIn a forest made of flesh\n\nWe move by instinct, darling\nLet our eyes like lepers drive\nThe doubters from our homes and\nInto the bottom of the sea\n\nAnd we speak in signals, darling\nLet our smoke stitch pictures\nLet us twist in patterns\nDull the horror of a city still on fire\n\nFor we are like medics handling\nSuicide by cyanide with bleeding fingers\nLet us suffer, completely inadequate\n\nAnd we move like lovers, lover\nLet me run my fingers down your side\nAnd kiss you right below the eye\nWe sleep with shadows but\nWe never give them bread\n\nOh horror, dress yourself in shame\nOr I will tear a hole in you, you harlot\nBurn your eyes\n\nI will hold your\nWhite-washed bones unto the sky and\nScream \"oh god, if you are there\nI hold this body to your judgment\nGive it your wrath or your mercy\nBut please pick wrath\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_6">Don\'t call this an art project\nThis is science, this is progress\nAnd don\'t pretend these are heartfelt words, we are\nChildren dressed as surgeons but disturbed by the sight of our scars\nAnd now we carry scalpels to trace the scarring resting somewhere\nOn the line between my house, your heart and into your home\nWhere you lay sleeping like a ceiling fan in winter\nGently turning as the wind reaches its fingers through the window\nJust to hold you, like I held you\nPressed like a rose between my fingers or like stones\nI keep in pockets meant to weigh me underwater\n\nThese scars will fade away but never disappear, my dear\nWe\'ll raise our fists like lightning to rods to god and\nIf he strikes us down\nThen he strikes us down\nBut first, let him hear us speak:\nWe are like the legacy of thunderstorms we watched and swore in doorways\n\"We will never be the same again.\"\n\nI can feel you healing and I hate it\nLike a harpist without hands you only bang the strings\nYou used to love to touch so much\nTo hear the dissonance drain violently and then dissolve\nLike all the songs I sang but never once could make you smile\nMy god, I would kill to make you smile\nAnd reach out to my hands, soft and frail\nTo make good on the love that you swear still exists, and still thrives\nThough we\'ve buried our bodies in blood and old lies\nLike, \"I\'m fine\" and \"you look so much better than him\"\nBut don\'t trust the surgeon with your heart\nShe\'s drunk and sips from poison cups, and\nDon\'t you trust the scientist\nHe says \"life is like a wineglass\" as he spills his drink\nLike secrets\nAll across your dress and says:\n\n\"My dear, I must confess\nI never thought you ever knew what love was like for real\nI never thought you needed me.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_7">Oh crashing airplane, where were you the day she left?\n\nUnderneath the laughs there lies a need\nThat nobody is getting\nAnd an honesty that doesn\'t stretch far enough\nTo show us all how much this will mean to us, my dear\nAnd when we\'re old we\'ll tell ourselves that we did\nEverything that we could to save this\nBut now we do nothing\n\nI\'ve slept for twenty years, but I\'ve acted strong at least\nIf you\'re leaving again, then you\'re leaving again\nAnd you\'re gone\nAnd I feel nothing anymore, so just keep walking away\nThirty-thousand steps\nI\'ll watch you for every second and never feel alone\n\nI\'ve been sleeping\nFor at least the last two years\nMy dear, my princess, my sister, my lover, my friend\nI made you a bed of thorns for every rose you ever left outside my door\nThat\'s all you ever left me\n\nLay your scars out in rows\nLay your scars out in rows\nLay your scars out in rows \nTo show me what I\'ve done to you\n\nLay your scars out in rows\nLay your scars out in rows\nIt was my weakness that couldn\'t save us\n\nSo lay your scars out in rows\nSo lay your scars out in rows\nSo lay your scars out in rows for me\n\nWe were one, and what are we now?\n\nAct strong, at least \nAnd don\'t turn around\nIf I\'m leaving, then I\'m leaving\nAnd I\'m leaving, and I\'m gone\n\nWe move as one</string>
    <string name="lyrics_vancouver_8">It\'s perfectly ok\nI\'m afraid, too</string>

    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_1">I think I saw you in my sleep, darling\nI think I saw you in my dreams you were\nStitching up the seams on every broken promise\nThat your body couldn\'t keep\nI think I saw you in my sleep\n\nI thought I heard the door open, oh no\nI thought I heard the door open but\nI only heard it close\n\nI thought I heard a plane crashing, but\nNow I think it was your passion snapping\n\nI think you saw me confronting my fear, it\nWent up with a bottle and went down with the beer and\nI think you ought to stay away from here\nThere are ghosts in the walls and they\nCrawl in your head through your ear\n\nI think I saw you in my sleep, lover\nI think I saw you in my dreams you were\nStitching up the seams on every mangled promise\nThat your body couldn\'t keep\nI think I saw you in my sleep</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_2">Up, M\'Lady, pack your things\nThis place is not your home\nNor was it ever, sever every tie\nTonight we ride, tonight we ride\n\nAnd how we\'ve trembled at the way that time\'s\nAssembled little fires of desire in the tundra of our skin\nSo, do yourself a little favor, savor every time you waver\nFor that shaking in my voice was only slyly feigned chagrin\nTonight we ride\n\nOh, Lover, uncover\nI know it\'s warm beneath your sheets\nAnd there is ice along the streets but listen\nLover, we will recover\nBut we\'ve no time to waste with meddling in affairs\nWe\'ve locked so tightly in our dreams\n\nWe are not clean, we are not pure\nWe can not rest until we\'re sure\nSo, rob your pretty little eyes of sleep\'s disguise\nI\'m at your bedside with a bucket full of lies\nSo, clear your ears and listen\n\nUp, M\'Lady, pack your things\nThis place is not your home\n\nBut I know what is\n\nAnd to the glorious past:\n\nYou\'ve opened my window but broken the glass\nAnd I beseech thee, \"shed thy beauty\"\nFor as a child leaves the womb and learns the cold\nYou have taught us perils in the present\nAnd you will bring us peril in our surely-soon-to-be\nUnless\n\nThe river\'s not flooded this time\n\nOh, precious distance\nOh, precious pain\nYou\'ve given me a name\nAnd etched it in the stones of the river bank\n\nOh, precious distance\nOh, precious pain\nYou\'ve given us a name\nYou\'ve given us a name\n\n\n\"Rise!\" Said the king to the river\n\"Never let up! No, bring us a flood and bring it hard!\"\n\"Freeze!\" Said the wind to the water\n\"Never give in, no, build us a bridge\nAnd build it strong and angry\nLet it still the king\'s decree\nOh, you must contemplate the current\nBoy, and command that coward cease\nThe boy breathes for his love says, \"I wait.\"\nHis love says, \"I wait.\"\nShe\'s shouting out, \"I will come back, yes, I will come back\nI will come, I have lived my life so uncomfortably \nDarling, come for me, come for me.\"\n\n\"Rise!\" Said the boy to his lover\n\"Darling, get up. I\'ve brought you my love, and brought it far!\"\n\"Leave!\" Said the girl to her lover\n\"I\'ve given in. If love is a bridge, we built it wrong!\"\n\nCurb your anger\nStill your fists\nShe will never come back, she\'ll never come back, she\'ll never come\nShe will never come back, she\'ll never come back, she\'ll never come</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_3">I\'ve come here as a man in shambles\nWorn out from begging on my knees\nPlease, I\'m just trying to keep my family together\nNow, when you saw you\'re lover wore a ring around her finger, why didn\'t you stop?\n\nI have half a mind to make you hurt, to make you bleed, to make you suffer\nI swear, if you\'ve touched her, oh heaven\nforgive what I would do to you, you monster\nAnd think about your children? \nThey\'ll never believe what you\'ve done\n\nListen, I\'m begging you, back off\nLet me rebuild all the things that you shattered\n\nShe meant it, I swear that she meant it, she whispered so often\n\"Husband, I\'ll always be here with you.\"\n\nBut always is always and always is valueless\nI wish I\'d never heard her speak a word\n\nAnd I hope you see us, your wife and your children and I\nBuried in the wreckage of your crime\nWhile you\'re laying down your sins\nSoftly leaning in to kiss your guilt goodnight\n\nShe is mine. You stole her, somehow tricked her but\nWe\'ll survive. We will. She loves me dearly, you\'ll see\nYou are blind, she loves me dearly\n\nBreathe in\n\nHe finally paused to take a breath \nThen looked down, it felt like staring into hell\nThe man was seated in a chair before him, silent\nA statue framed in pain and flesh. He thought\n\"Oh, what more can I say to sway him? To make this statue speak? \nI swear he\'s made of stone and I am barely stirring up a breeze.\"\n\nAnd after waiting in the silence\nFinally turned around to leave\nBroken and barely through the doorway\nBreathing slowly, beating hard, he heard him speak:\n\n\"I guess love\'s a funny thing, the way it fades away without a warning\nIt doesn\'t ask to be excused\nAnd when it\'s gone, oh it\'s gone, and it ain\'t ever comin\' back\n\nThere is nothing you can do to save it\nTo make it breathe the way it did when you were sliding on the ring\nTrust me, It\'s gone for good\n\nNow there is nothing you can do to stop me\nShe is happy when she is with me and I am finally alive. I\'m sorry.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_4">She forced a smile, said\n\"Boy, come kiss my mouth, I\'ll set you free\nYou know that hope you\'re holding to? It looks an awful lot like fear\nNow, you\'re so quick to fall on failure, and so quick to raise your voice, like\n\'If I can\'t find a mistake to blame, we didn\'t have a choice.\'\n\nNo, but you had option\nI was your chance to feel complete\nBut when I leaned in close to you\nyou kissed your fear instead of me\n\nYou had my hand in your hand\nYou had my lip in your teeth\nYou had my heart on your sleeve\nYou had a chance to breathe\n\nBut, boy, you wouldn\'t let your fear recede so I moved on\n\nAnd it\'s too late to change your mind now\nYou got scared, boy, and I got gone\nNow you failed, and there\'s no way to turn back time\nYou had your chance, boy, I tried.\"\n\n\"You tried?\" I looked her in the eye and smiled\n\"My girl, you must understand that fear is not some product that I made\nIt crept unwelcome in my head the day they had her torn away\nIt changed me\n\nNow at the end of everyday I lie awake at night and wait\nTo feel the wires of my brain get cut and quietly rearranged, and\nHear my beaten heart exclaim, \'Still, I refuse to let her go.\'\n\nSo we escape to our mistakes for they wait patiently for us\nOh, how they always wait for me\n\nIf my fear has kept me here only my fear can set me free\n\nAnd I\'m sorry, dear, but don\'t you dare say another word\nHow could I risk holding your heart in me while still in love with her?\n\nYou were wrong.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_5">Out where the stones lay like bones by the ocean\nOut where the waves crash contempt on the land\nSomeone was trembling for fear of the tempest\nSomebody silently reached for their hand\nSaid, understand that if you\'re cold I\'ll keep you warm\nAnd besides, there\'s so much beauty in a storm\nSo come down with me to the shore\nAnd what\'s more, I adore you\nSo tell me, what is there to fear\nYou think some seraph up above is trying to rob us of our love\nBecause the sky\'s not clear\nMy dear, you know there\'s not\nNow listen to the rain upon the rooftop\nBut the wind picked up\n\nOut where the stones stand up like thrones beside the ocean\nOut where the waves make a grave of the sea\nThe lovers struggled in the middle of the tempest\nAnd water angrily crawled up onto the beach\nSaid, hold my hand and stay with me\nWe\'ll be released\nBut the tide clung like an anchor to her feet\nAnd though he tried to make the water line recede\nIt pulled her out into the sea\nHe could not break apart the waves to bring her safely back in\nHe watched her hand break through the surface once\nThen disappear again\nForever wait inside the sea for my, my dear\nI hear you\nYou speak in every curling wave\nAnd sing in every violent breeze\nSomeday not far away from here\nMy dear, I swear I\'ll see you\nAnd we will hear the seraphs cry\nFor they will still envy you and I\nHow they envied you and I\nHow they envied you and I\nHow they envied you and I</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_6">Oh, we could blame it on our hands\nThey lifted the drink to our mouths so we drank it\nOr we could blame it on our bodies\nThey say, we like the way we feel when we get touched\nYou\'ve got your fingers snared in my veins\nI think it\'s time you pulled them out\nAnd I don\'t care about the flesh it\'ll tear\nIt isn\'t flesh that I\'m worried about\n\nWe held a match to keep our sight on the path\nBut the flame gave up and we lost it\nAnd I\'ve knelt for the last three years\nTrying to find it back with the blackened matchstick\nToday I\'m not afraid of failure\nThe past is a flower\nThe future, the snow\nI wasn\'t ever close to perfect\nBut I never let you go\n\nYou let your doubt lead you like a river on and on\nAnd you will never get back to save what you had\nHear me promise\nI will bury your problems in me\nSo sleep soundly\nI held your heart in my fingers\nNow it\'s gone, it\'s gone, it\'s gone and you will never admit\nThat you bid the wind blow the flames out\nAnd buried the coals in the sea\nYou tricked me\n\nYou came back and you brought floods\nWearing a necklace made of hearts that you\'d dragged through the mud\nAnd I guess I wasn\'t quite sure what to say to you\nBut then I saw mine, almost reached out to grab it\nSaid, darling, you\'re the only one on earth I want to have it\nBut now I\'m not so sure that was true\nAfter the hell you put it through\nBut there was no sharp pain this time\nJust the ghost of your presence compressing my chest like a vine\nAn unshakable absence\nLike most of my insides crawled out of my mouth and went west\nBut that\'s fine\nWe cast our hearts in plaster\nWe imagined our bodies were fashioned of stone\nBut they chipped at the brick and mortar\nWe found out that we\'re only layers of skin hiding bones\nAnd our bones are like chains, old and rusted in the rain\nThey\'re going to snap when the weight shifts\n\nYou moved like a fire through the forest\nYour hands were as red as the skin on your lips\nYou\'d been flirting with distance, princess\nI tasted its spit in your kiss\nOh mistress, know\nToday I will bury the flames of your failure\nThe past is a liar\nThe future, a whore\nI\'ll lay your bones into the earth and you will haunt my head no more\nOh, we could blame it on our hands\nOh, we could blame it on our hands\nBut it was our mouths that opened up to swallow\nOh, we could blame it on our hands\nAnd our heads that commanded us drink\nBut as I buried your flames in the dirt\nI watched the smoke pull your ghost from the grave\nAnd I fear they\'ll only lay in wait\nUntil we are face to face again\nJust when I said, I\'m moving, I\'m moving on\nI felt them come to life again and again and again and again\n\nThere are fires\nThat tear through valleys and make dust from grass\nThere are fires\nThere are wires\nBound in blue light, they pull us to the past\nThere are wires\nWe are tired\nWe should have known from the start that this wouldn\'t last\nWe are tired</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_7">My precious wife, I am in shambles\nI am crumbling, I am\nWas it something I did\nBid the tide to climb so high that it ripped our shore up\nI can fix it, I swear\nIf you trust me\nI am old and I am rusting but I care\nI care\n\nMy precious wife, we made a promise\nPledged our flesh to be one\nHow can you doubt a love that stood so proud as we raised our children\nI believe in it still\nIt has faltered and it has faded\nBut I know it\'s there\nHow\'d it change\nThe way you thought of me\nHow strange to think we once were lovers\nNow we\'ve wrapped the past up in broken glass\nAnd when you speak my name you shudder\nOh precious wife, believe I\'ll save this\nI\'ll revive it, I will\nWe\'ve built a family from this marriage\nWhy would you tear it apart\n\nOh speak now, precious\nYour silence screams\nYou\'re giving in to failure\nHear me, the promise that you made was meant to live forever\nUntil our deathbed, you\'re not allowed to change your mind\nWas there nothing in that promise\nAre you listening to me\n\nOh husband, I could not control it\nHusband, I could not abstain\nOne cannot stop the wind from blowing\nNor refuse the falling rain\nLove stirred up a storm inside me\nWrapped its arms around my waist\nI failed you dear, I\'m sorry, oh I\'m sorry\nThere was nothing I could do\nNo, there was nothing I could\nSure as the rain will fall\nSome love just fails without reason\nThere is nothing you can do\nThere is nothing you can do\nThere is nothing you can do\nThere is nothing you can do</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_8">Now speak of anger\nForget all the fears you\'ve kept about love and sex and death and faith\nErased, or swinging sweet from around her neck and between her breasts\nLet every lonely body finally break its fear of flesh and say\n\"How strange it must\'ve been back when we shook at the sight of sweat.\"\n\nLet our worries wander out of like water streaming from a spring\nAnd sing of all the things our heads have failed to ruin yet\nThere\'s so much they have failed to ruin yet\nBright as lightning, loud as thunder\nWe\'ll move all the hurt aside to let love sustain our passions\nAnd move up and onward\n\nWe are not our losses, we are only the extent to which we love\nSo build a home for your family, and build a castle for your friends\nNow set their beds with sheets and blanketã, keep them safe until the end\nI\'ve felt the damage and burn from the fallout\nMy love failed but theirs prevailed\nMy friends, I\'m only flesh and bone\nBut I won\'t let you die alone\n\nSo leave our hearts at the foot of the mountain\nLet our burdens be locked in the stone\nIf you will help me roll it upward\nI won\'t let you die alone\n\nI see a beauty springing upward from the earth and from out our hearts\nFor all the bad that seems to plague us, I swear to you there\'s good\nThey say that death is not a problem, it\'s a promise\nI can only say for sure that when it makes your bed I\'ll kiss your head \"Goodnight.\"\n\nSo speak of all the love we lost, and what it cost us\nLeft us beg our breath to stop but we kept on and\nWe were strong. We stayed bright as lightning\nwe sang loud as thunder, we moved ever forward\nWe are not our failures\nWe are love</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_9">You still cross my mind from time to time, and I mostly smile\nStill so set on finding out where we went wrong and why\nSo I retrace our every step with an unsure pen\nTrying to figure out what my head thinks\nBut my head just ain\'t what it used to be\nAnd then again, what\'s the point anyway?\n\nI remember you ascending all the stairs up to the balcony\nTo see if you could see me hidden quietly away\nAnd I remember the skin of your fingers\nThe spot three quarters up I\'d always touch when I was out of things to say\nYou held my hand, but you were too afraid to speak and I could never understand\nI remember when you leaned in quick to kiss me, and I swear\nThat not a single force on earth could stop the trembling of my hand\n\nAnd I remember how you smiled through the smoke\nIn a crowded little coffeehouse and laughed at all my jokes\nAnd I remember the way that you dressed and\nHow we wasted all the best of us in alcohol and sweat\nAnd I remember when I knew that you\'d be leaving, how I barely kept up breathing\nand I bet if I had to do it all again, I\'d feel the same pain\nAnd I remember panicked circles in the terminal in tears\nHow I wept to god in fits. I\'ve hated airports ever since\n\nIt must be true what people say, that only time can heal the pain\nAnd every single day I feel it fade away, but\nI still remember how the distance tricked us\nAnd lead us helpless by the wrist into a pit to be devoured\nI still remember how we held so strong to this\nThough we had never really settled on a way out\nI still remember the silence, and how we\'d always find a way\nTo turn and run to our mistakes\n\nI still remember how it all came back together just to fall apart again\nMy dear, I hear your voice in mine\nI\'ve been alone here, I\'ve been afraid, my dear\nI\'ve been at home here\nYou\'ve been away for years\nI\'ve been alone\n\nI breathed your name into the air\nI etched your name into me\nI felt my anger swelling\nI swam into its sea\n\nI held your name inside my heart\nBut it got buried in my fear\nIt tore the wiring of my brain\nI did my best to keep it clear\n\nSo, dear, no matter how we part\nI hold you sweetly in my head\nAnd if I do not miss a part of you\nA part of me is dead\n\nIf I can\'t love you as a lover\nI will love you as a friend\nAnd I will lay a bed before you\nKeep you safe until the end</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_10">I spoke too soon, it seems, for you made a home in my dreams\nWhile I slept you kept running yourself through my head\nLike, \"I won\'t be dead yet.\" I said, \"You don\'t understand\nWe had no control, they stole it; love\'s been so unfair to me.\"\n\n\"But see, boy, that\'s my point. You must move on.\"\nThen felt her ghost move in me\nI heard her voice call out my name but this time it faded out away\n\"I\'ll bury it today.\"\n\nSo I breathed her name out into a cold, cold room\nwatched her ghost ascend the walls and then dissolve\n\"This time I choose to let her go\nI will not let my fear become the only world I\'ve ever known\nI know my heart, kiss my mouth, set me free; I\'ve wounds to mend\nAnd we\'ll be more than friends, my dear\nI fear I\'ve changed my mind again.\"\n\"But boy, you\'re too late. Oh, God, it\'s too late.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_11">They stored their passion in the creases in the corners of their mouths\nEvery angle of light from the open window washed their aged faces out\nThey said, \"Should we feel guilty for this sin? \nLord, did we kill a man and woman just to lie here skin to skin?\"\n\n\"I wasn\'t happy. I wasn\'t happy where I was\nWhat is life without a purpose? What is purpose without love?\nI pray my children will forgive me, though I bade the river flood\nI have washed my hands a thousand times but still can see the blood.\"\n\n\"Oh, great mercy, I am here to beg forgiveness for this mess\nI know I tore two worlds apart but I can\'t change the way I felt\nLove swept in like a storm and ripped the hinges from the doors\nLove poured in like a flood, I couldn\'t stop it anymore. I will not be drowned.\"\n\nShe said, \"Lover, come and hold me, I am terribly afraid\nWhile you\'re shouting at the stars, my scars are not fading away.\"\nHe said, \"Darling, I was begging heaven make them disappear, but\nSee, I didn\'t get an answer or at least one I could hear\n\nNow, I am thinking of the past and how we both said vows and lied and \nI am wondering how we trust ourselves to say a second time:\n\n\'To have and to hold\nFrom this day and onward\nFor better and for worse\nFor richer and for poorer\nIn sickness or in health\nTo love and to cherish \nTill death do us part?\'\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_12">I felt your sickness brush against my arm as I walked by you\nHeard your voice but couldn\'t tell that it was you\nAnd, slowly, watched your sickness slip away into a place\nThat I\'d once feared but I was not afraid this time\nSo I gave chase and found it, finally, slowly feeding from your head\nAnd from my friends, and from my family, so I grabbed it by the neck\n\"For every lover you have ruined\" I dug my nails into its flesh\n\"And every life that you have taken\"\nSlammed its head against the brick\nIts blood poured out onto the pavement\nI stirred it in with dirt and spit\n\"I will take a part of you.\"\nI made mortar from the mix\nTore every organ from its body\nBroke its bone and fashioned bricks\nI laid the mortar in between\nI made a throne for hope to sit\n\"Too long you\'ve torn us into pieces\nFirmly held onto our wrists. Today I bury you in me.\"\nI swallowed every inch of it\n\nI\'ll hold you, as you have held me\nYou\'ve held me in your heart, we\'ll be set free from fear\nWe\'ve felt our failures\nWe\'ve watched our passions leave, but we\'re still breathing on\nI\'ll hold you, as you have held me\nYou\'ve held me in your heart\nAnd I will hold you in my heart\n\nBut I still see him dead in the parking lot at the gas station just down the street\nAnd I still hear my friend say\n\"You know, you wouldn\'t believe the things I saw when I was stationed overseas.\"\nBut he somehow keeps smiling in spite all of that\nWhile I keep finding ways to push the good out for the bad\nOh, how selfish of myself to always say that it was more than I could take\nLike it was pain I could not shake\nLike it could break me with its fingers, throw my body in the lake\nAnd I would slowly sink away\nBut the Truth is it was sorrow that I made and would not face\nSee, I keep falling for the future after tripping on the past\nAnd I am always tearing sutures out to make the anguish last like it defines me\nOr reminds me I\'ve found comfort in my suffering\nAnd uncertainty in happiness and death\nBecause what\'s next is such a mystery to me\nI am terrified of all the things I feel but cannot see\nFriends and family, put your hand into my hand and lay your head into my chest\nYou are all that I have left here\nWe are all that we have left\nWe are the lovers, We are the last of our kind\nLink your arms and keep your chin up\nAnd I swear that we\'ll be fine\nWe are the lovers, We are the last of our kind\nThough we\'re not sure who we are, we keep our heads up \nThough we\'re not sure where we\'re from, we keep our hearts up\nThough we\'re not sure when we\'ll leave, we keep our heads up \nThough we\'re not sure where we\'ll go, we keep our hopes up\n\nKeep your head up; we\'re fine. Just keep your head up; I swear we\'ll be alright\nKeep your head up. Oh, my friends, keep your head up, and I swear we\'ll never die\nI swear we\'ll get home safe and sound, we\'ll live on underground\nI will give your heart a place to rest when everything you had has turned and left\nI\'ll weave your names into my ribcage; lock your hearts inside my chest\nRegain the passion I once carried; do away with all the rest\nI tore the sickness from your bodies; smashed its head against the bricks\nI made a castle from its bones that you may always dwell in it\nSo sing for every buried moment that you\'d thought would never end\nAnd sing your fears about the future; and a dirge for faded friends\nFor all the love that you had held to, why it somehow failed to keep\nAnd sing each minute you\'ve been frightened; every hour that you\'ve lost sleep\nAnd sing for all your friends and family; sing for those who didn\'t survive\nBut sing not for their final outcome; sing a song of how they tried\nWe live amidst a violent storm; leaves us unsatisfied at best\nSo fill your heart with what\'s important, and be done with all the rest\nWe are what\'s left of what we once were\nWe are falling far behind\nThere\'s so much stacking up against us and we\'re running out of time\n\nWe are but hopeful children, and we\'re the last of our kind\nBut if we let our hearts move outward, I know we will never\nWe are but friends and family, we are the last of our kind\nSo hold my hand, I\'ll lift your head up, and I promise we\'ll be fine\nWe are but hopeful lovers, and we are running out of time\nThere\'s so much stacking up against us, and we\'re falling far behind\nWe are but hopeful lovers, we are the last of our kind\nBut if we let our hearts move outward, I know we will never\nWe are but lovers, we are the last of our kind\nAnd if we let our hearts move outward, I know we will never\nWe are but lovers, we are the last of our kind\nAnd if we let our hearts move outward, we will never die</string>
    <string name="lyrics_satbotrbvaa_13">I know that someday you\'ll be sleeping, Darling, likely dreaming off the pain\nI hope you\'ll hear me in the streetlight\'s humming, softly breathing out your name\nI know that even with the seams stitched tightly, darling, scars will remain\nI say we scrape them from each other, darling, and let them wash off in the rain\nAnd when they run into the river, oh no, let the water not complain\nI swear that even with the distance, slowly wearing out your name\nYour hands still catch the light the right way and\nOur hearts still beat the same\nAnd our hearts still beat the same</string>

    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_1">To scratched out, for everything.\nNight fell on me writing this and I ran out of paper so I crossed the name out at the top of the page. Not sure why I\'m even writing this. But I guess it feels right. It sort of feels like I have to-like an exorcism.\n\nI guess that makes me sound crazy but that\'s alright. Lately I feel like I might be, not that I\'ve heard any voices or anything. Just like that everyday kind, where you forget things you shouldn\'t and you think too much about death.\n\nMaybe you know what I\'m talking about. Or maybe you would have known? Or had known?\nIs it once knew? I don\'t know what tense to use.\n\nI know I never used to feel like this. I used to never think of death or hear voices. I used to feel Like everything was perfectly in order, a normal life, but I guess then came a departure.\nThat I know you understand (or would\'ve understood?). I guess things changed after that, and I\'m mostly scared now.\nBut it\'s there in the stories, or whatever they are. You can see it. Anybody could if they could Look. I wrote some notes in the margins explaining it. The rest is in between lines or in the fine Print. First, the feeling of abandonment, then trying to cope. Then death and hope and the thing Itself, waiting for me. It\'s all there in the pages ahead of here. It\'s there waiting for you.\nOr for me. I\'m not sure.\nThe whole story.</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_2">Like a shadow on a shadow, a phantom in a film strip\nFaint glimmer of the past trapped in mother\'s old slides\nSits still in the apartment while sifting through some pictures\nOf the child that he once was and the sense of hope they framed\n\"It\'s a shame\"\n\nAnd I fear that fate while the humming from the street keeps me awake\n\nHe says, \"I let life get twisted\nGet worn out, torn up, and late with the rent\nAnd now nothing makes sense except the bench and that piano\nA feeling nearing order when I\'m pressing down the chords.\"\nAnd he plays\n\nAnd it swells and breaks, but what\'ll it take to make my life sound like that\n\nAnd brings a fever, a dream of sweat and ecstasy\nA kiss on every hammer hit that follows as the keys fall down and\nBring an order first, then chaos, then a calm, that\nPaints every shift in murals on the wall\nAnd it presses to your neck\nIt clutches to your hips\nSoftly sings to you of fireworks and God and art and sex and it\'s strange\nThat it feels so right when nothing else does\n\nBut all the while he\'s playing there\'s a humming\nComing up and through the window from outside\nAnd even he has to admit a certain melody in it, but then why can\'t he harmonize?\nIt\'s like the city\'s got it\'s own song but he can\'t play along\nHe sees the notes as they fly by but always plays them wrong\nAnd in the bathroom it gets blurry, gets warm and distorted\nLike light pushed the orange of the pillbox he poured in\nHis palm. It falls to the floor, he smiles as it hits\n\"Sounds a little like an instrument.\"\n\nLike a voice in the choir, that hum and that drumbeat of life as an art-form and\nFire through the streets that keep moving us in silence to phantom baton sweeps\nKeep tapping to the tempo of our feet\n\nAnd all the ones who seem to fit the best into the chorus never notice there\'s a song\nAnd the ones who seem to hear it end up tortured by the chords when they fail to find\nA way to sing along\n\nAnd when you sing the wrong thing it all starts collapsing\nStarts to ring out and feedback, starts lapsing and crashing, on notes that don\'t clash\nBut that never quite feel like they match\n\nAnd I never quite feel like mine match\n\nThere\'s a melody in everything\nI\'m trying to find a harmony but\nNothing seems to work\nNothing seems to fit\n\nThere\'s a melody in everything\nI\'m trying to find a harmony but\nNothing seems to work\nNothing seems to fit\n\nThere\'s a melody in everything\nI\'m trying to find a harmony but\nNothing seems to work\nNothing fits</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_3">Stained glass and the choir sing out that strong and ceaseless chorus here\nSo sweet the voices, sweep like leaves into the street\nOn Eastern, a celebration carried on for God and hope and refuge\nTo keep each other, life; give shelter from the storm. And keep warm\nThe congregation gathers outside in the parking lot, each service done\nThey keep the old hymn rolling on and on and\nI see the scene in color each day driving out to Eastown\nThat old abandoned church and have I gone the same sad way?\n\nHave I gone the same sad way?\n\nThrough the sixties flourished and the seventies in flux\nThe eighties fluctuate each year unclear of when the money would dry up\nAnd when the nineties violent crime and rising unemployment rates came by\nThat parking lot grew dim and thin of sinners and saints\nUntil the voices, unceasing, slowly faded to black\nUntil the weeds stormed the concrete from unattended cracks\nIt had to know, had to feel that glory never coming back\nLike I could feel it when the passion left, the last of what I had\nIt had to know like I knew\nAnd I can\'t find it still\nMight not ever\n\nTen years now standing vacant\nTen years on empty, maybe more\nOnce held the faith of hundreds\nSoon one more cell phone store\nFor years they gathered here\nInside the building sound and true\nTo sing their praises to a god that gave them hope\nTo carry on, to carry through\nSo, I\'ve been thinking about that\nSometimes go slow when I drive by\nHow a home of stone and a house so holy\nGrows so empty over time\nWhat gave those people purpose\nPast death approaching constantly\nNow left to crumble slowly\nNow left to wither with the weeds\nNow left to ice and vandals\nThe advent candles long since gone\nThe old foundation shifting hard\nThe concrete overgrown, but\nThat stained-glass window sits untouched amongst the brickwork worn\nA symbol of the beauty only perfect at that moment we were born\nAnd just the other day I swear I saw a man there\nPulling weeds out of the concrete, sweeping up and patching cracks\nI saw him lift a rag to wash the years of filth from off those windows\nMade me wonder if there\'s anyone like that for you and me and\nAnybody else who broke and lost hope</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_4">An outcry\nTo lost dreams and sense of wonder\nTo the streets that raised him\nSay \"Goodbye\" to the hope for the home he\'d been holding\nSay \"Goodbye\" and \"Be gone\" and \"Be great.\"\nTo the friends who left when they still could\nFor the ones who chose to stay to waste away unplaced\nAlone, and pray\nTo get out\nTo grow old\nTo grow strong and\nLeave this city, so familiar all it\'s places\nAll these memories turn each day more to gray\nMore they space out till it\'s once a year we\'ll catch up, maybe less\nOr else just daydreams while he\'s working late\nThinks only of those friends and when they left\n\"Are we still friends at all, my friends?\"\n\nCan I leave?\n\nRewind and find a younger man\nAll hopes and goals and dreams alight and\nBright with friendship at the crossroads in the night\n\"Now make a choice,\" the city said\nWe were barely twenty then\nBut while I swore it my allegiance\nThey chose leaving, all my friends\nAnd now it\'s letters, maybe phone calls\nThat come less and less each year\nAll addressed with wives and children\nTo the fool who chose to stay here\nAnd it hurts me to know I\'m alone now\nAnd it\'s worse when I know that I chose it\nDon\'t make the same mistake as me\nDon\'t make the same mistake\n\nAnd now my friends have all left\nOr it\'s been me gone all along\nI guess we all part one day and drop like leaves into The breeze\nAnd ain\'t it wild? Ain\'t it bitter?\nDidn\'t it carry you from me?\nBut it\'s the coping with my fear that keeps me here\nSee, once it\'s gone you can\'t retrieve it\nDo I regret you? Can I forget you?\nI still believe I might get left here\nI Might turn 63 still sweeping up the gutters in the street or weeding concrete\nWait and see, we\'ll wait and see\nOr, rather, I will, only me\nOnly me\n\nDon\'t make the same mistake as me\nSay \"Goodbye\" and \"Be gone\" and \"Be great\" and be done and be free</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_5">Everybody wants a reason for everything\nIt\'s so much easier with someone or something to blame\n\nI\'ve always struggled at the root of the problem\nHas it been absence or my constant lack of defense\n\nI\'ve never spent a lot on finding a remedy\nI guess I figured that it hurt for a reason\nI guess that\'s why I\'ve always turned to writing it down\nNot just in stories, but the letters in between\nAnd I guess that\'s why it haunts the pages of everything\nTo self-examine\n\nI think the thing is that I shut off from everything\nFrom friends and family and my own ambitions\nFrom having fun\nI just shut off from everything\n\nSelf-defeating? Yeah, probably\nBut I don\'t know that I had total control over it\nAnd I\'m not sure it even matters why\n\nSometimes things happen and you can\'t do anything\nPlus, I\'m the only one who deals with it anyway\nSo if everyone could do me a favor and\nJust put their fingers down\nI\'d, and keep your mouths\n\nSorry, I know I seem angry\nI\'m not, I promise, I just know I did this to me\nAnd I will deal with it accordingly\n\nAnd I don\'t need opinions from those never a part of it\nDon\'t need them pointing out my problems, they\'re mine\nDon\'t need reminders, I know better than anyone\n\nAnd yeah, I know, I should be finding another way\nI know that I should be out seeking a substitute\nBut just forgetting never really made sense to me\n\nSo I haven\'t been\n\nDo I feel embarrassed about it?\nI think you know the answer to that\nI think you\'d probably feel a little bit embarrassed for me\nWouldn\'t you\n\nI know I should\'ve moved on ages ago, been happy already\nBut it\'s never been that easy for me\nOr maybe it was me that made it so hard\n\nI know I\'ve only ever tried a handful of times\nTo sever this thing torturing me\nIt never got me anywhere, with anyone\nNo friendship or hobby, no lover\'s bed worked\n\nBut looking back I maybe never tried hard enough\nAnd it is my fault\n\nMaybe I never tried at all</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_6">I\'ve been watching a slow thaw come around\nI\'ve been waiting in the cold and hazy blue\nI\'ve been driving alone out to the edge of town\nI\'ve been thinking too much of you\n\nLast snowfall left splinters and some winters never end\nNeither wane nor wear\nAnd sunshine is like lovers and some summers just pretend\nOnly warm the air\nIt\'s that I\'m tired of the feeling here\nIt\'s too near to death, it\'s too jobless year-round\nIt\'s not the weather in the city or the highway moan\nNot the streets or the buildings, neither wooden nor stone\nEvery reason to leave this place behind, why I should be alone\nAre made of flesh and bone\n\nI\'ve been thinking of exile\nI\'ve been thinking hit the highway and head up North\nI\'ve been thinking cross the bridge and don\'t turn back\nThe only warmth is a warmth alone\n\nHe packed up, took 75 northbound to a brand new life and\nWaved goodbye to the world in the rearview mirror\nSaw it clearer in hindsight\nThe shape of its skyline traced in a flame from the windows ablaze\nThe people restless and the streetlights glowing like\nMany beacons in the sea or like a lantern lit\nFor the ones still lost out in the dead of the night\nLike lightning striking darkness once, no thunder, no pain\n\nHave you ever watched a slow thaw come around?\nHave you waited in the cold and hazy blue?\nThere\'s an airport there out near the edge of town\nI\'ve been thinking too much of you\n\nSettled in that still forest like another phantom\nOr another shadow cast by choice\nA noiseless chorus blows through the leaves and trees\nAnd brings a peace at last\nFrom a place where the song kept changing\njust when he was starting to get it\n\nWhen he was starting to trust there\'d be a day\nHe\'d find a way to keep the rust at-bay\nThere\'d be a day he\'d find a hum to help him muffle the past\nLike thunder underwater, he hears it fading\nAnd feels no pain at all\n\nTo a boring, desperate city\nIt\'s been weeks since I\'ve been around you\nHas the fear begun to fade away like sunlight\nWhen it sinks into the lake?\nAre they now building up, or breaking down\nAnd boarding up the fronts?\nHas the whole town been foreclosed now?\nAnd what happened to those youthful dreams\nSunk deep in the river weak?\nOr got tangled up in weeds or else they\'re stumbling drunk\nOn Wealthy Street? Or making plans to leave?\nI need to leave. I can\'t marry this place\nI won\'t bury the past. I just need a change of scenery\nI will hold these old streets sweetly in my head like her\nAnd I will praise their bravery always and again\nLet tongues confess the plague of joblessness\nA temporary illness\nLet us wave their flag from there to here then over\nAnd again and let us hope for better things\nThough we may not ever get them\n\nWe will rise again from ashes one day\nUntil then, just roll me away\nI need to leave but swear I will carry you in me until the end\n\nSo, Tuebor, my home!\n\nYour desperate friend</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_7">After sundown, before sleeping, I am the worst of me. I am a mess of these\nOld themes and the murmur of half-dreams whisper seductively and\nStage scenes\nIt\'s fear fiction, these visions, caught somewhere between delusion and prophesy\nWhat I haven\'t done, what I\'ve wanted to, and what I fear you have\nBecomes reality here\n\nBright lights in the young night keep to the beat\nA classic party scene, crowded and interesting\nNo love, no life, no history\nJust touch, just chemistry, just\nA roaring undercurrent simple and sensory\nYoung bodies, warm skin, perfect symmetry and\nIt\'s a moment, harmless. It\'s energy\nIt\'s like medicine\nIt\'s self-discovery\n\nSee, all the secrets I keep, why are they secrets?\n\nIt\'s only temporary, that fleeting feeling of warmth\nJust a flash before the line gets blurry\nBetween a longing for more than what the body wants now and\nWhat the body wants now more than anything\nWas it integrity that kept my hands to myself or\nJust the thought of getting too far ahead of you?\nWas it that I got too tired of the consequence?\nOr was I just scared?\n\nI only know I never wanted to get left behind\n\nNo pauses, not a second guess\nFirst a swaying then a stumble then a swagger\nThey\'re just movements towards feeling. It doesn\'t matter\nNeither hesitates to carry on a kind of energy\nSweat and block out everything to\nFind every aperture and compel the animal parts\nFan flames, taste fruit, taste bitter fruit\nJust trying to learn how all the wires in the body work\nJust trying to feel it out, it\'s like medicine\nTrap the healing in whatever bed they end up in\n\nI want to feel it out. I want to know how it works\nI want to know if it was worth it to worry\nAbout the ghosts I feared would haunt the memory\nAbout the damage that I\'m sure the fear has done to me now\nI want to know what it is in me that won\'t follow through\nThose nights the instinct takes a hold of me and pushes too\nMaybe it\'s only that I\'ve never gotten over you\n\nOr am I still scared?\n\nI see the church steps, a vision. Is there fiction in this one too?\nIt\'s true, I\'ve made a tale of it here, still, it\'s a little unclear who\'s been haunting who\nAnd time can be such a funny thing, always moving to the future\nGlorifying the past and amplifying the pain in frames and glass\nSo was our touch half as sacred as I\'ve made it seem\nOr just another fabrication of a half-dream?\nJust those chemicals, the adolescent love\nJust us trying to grasp onto meaning\nOnto a purpose\nOnto a sense that\nSomething spiritual releases when the feeling hits\n\nAnd when the feeling hits\n\nAnd in that moment sparks and harps play out\nA sweeping melody through fog and fantasy\nAnd in that moment there\'s an honesty instinctive and pure but\nIt departs like it came, rapid and bearing no more\nThan fleeting ecstasy of natural harmony\nThey fear the notes being played and try to sing along\nDon\'t be ashamed, be free to the feeling. Don\'t be ashamed, keep feeling\nBut find it: a body that makes sense\n\nI\'ve felt it</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_8">Third time writing you a letter, getting darker. I’m getting worse and worse\n\nI had a reason for the writing, but trying to exorcise my demons didn’t work\nTo try to rid me of The worry and to purge you out of wonder for the future and the hurt\nI wrote a poem:\n\nI’m increasingly aware I’ve been painting things in gray\nI’m increasingly alarmed by the pain\nI’m increasingly alive to every cloud up in the sky\nI’m increasingly afraid it’s going to rain\n\nSee, lately I’ve hated me for over-playing pain\nFor always pointing fingers out at everyone\nBut Who in fact is guilty and for picking at my scabs\nLike they could never break but they can\nAnd They will and I’ll spill like a leak in the basement\nA drunk in the night choir\nJust slur all those Words to make deadbeat that sweet old refrain\nSelf-inflicting my pain and therein lies the real shame\nI heard when they were picking through the rubble\nFinding limbs, they sang hymns, but Now what of what I sing?\n\nThe worry, the wonder, the shortness of days\nThe replacement for purpose\nThe things swept away by\nThe worry, the wonder, my slightness of frame\nThe replacements for feeling\nThe casual lay\nThe worst of the wildlife wears clothes and can pray and\nThe worry, the wonder, for three meals a day\nOnly death unimpeded, not slowing it’s pace\nBrings that petty, old worry and wonder away</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_9">Another shooting on the southeast side. This a drive-by, mid-day\nOutside of the bus stop, by Fuller and Franklin. Or near there\nNot far from the park. About a block from where the other shooting was last month\nOr was it last week?\n\nShots were fired from an SUV heading northbound, Eastown\nThe target a rival but they didn\'t hit the target this time\nThey hit a kid we think had nothing to do with it\n\nAnd I travel backwards through time and space and I disintegrate, become invisible\nI want to see it where I couldn\'t when it happened\nI want to see it all first hand this time\nI want to know what it felt like\n\nSo I float behind police lines, reconstruct the scene in fragments of memories\nI want to know what his mother looked like up close, I want to see her leaning over his body\nSo I float there, transcend time. I want to capture it accurately\nI want to know what the color of the blood was spilling out from the tarp onto the concrete\nI want to write it all down so I can always remember\nIf you could see it up close how could you ever forget how senseless death, how precious life\nI want to be there when the bullet hit\n\nAnd the crowd poured out as the shots drowned into siren sounds, out of there houses now\nAnd over front yards, all the way up to the place where the police tape ran to mark the crime\nScene. Everybody trying to catch a glimpse of what was happening\nOf what was going on between the ambulance and all the cop cars\nEverybody gossiping, \"Whose kid got hit? Where\'d it hit him? And who could\'ve fired it?\"\nEverybody wondering, \"How did it happen again? And is he dead? These children. Our kids.\"\nEverybody wondering how far they were from where the victims lived\n\nAnd I visit them, their houses. Inside my dream I visit them\nMy spirit, soaring high and high up over King Park, leaves the crime scene, travels further back\nTill far before the shooting, through their windows, to their living rooms\nI see them younger this time, playing games and doing homework\nAll these marks of youth soon transformed coldly into stone for fights and stupid feuds\nFor ruins wrapped in gold. And cruelly I recall why I have come: To find a reason\nBut there cannot be a reason, not for death, not like this. Not like this\n\nThree days later they made funeral plans, the family\nThree days later a mother had to bury her son\n\nNot far away the shooter holed up in a hotel near to the highway with a friend and the gun\nThat same gun. He\'d fled immediately but was identified by witnesses, his picture on TV\nOnly 20 years old, they called him \"Grandpa.\" He was older than the others by a year\nMaybe two\n\nAnd he was safe for awhile until somebody saw him there and notified the authorities\nWho surrounded the hotel, first arresting an accomplice while attempting to flee\nThen chasing him up the staircase to the floor where he\'d stayed. He closed the door hard\nBehind him, locked himself in the room\n\nThey could\'ve kicked in the door but knew the gun was still with him\nOne he\'d already used and so they feared what he\'d do\nI floated up through the window of a room to the West\nI hovered out to the hallway, tried to listen in\nI heard them trying to reason, get him to open the door\nHis uncle begging and pleading, half-collapsed to the floor\nHe preached of hope and forgiveness\nSaid, \"There is always a chance to rectify what you\'ve taken, make your peace in the world.\"\nI thought to slip through the door, I could\'ve entered the room\nI felt the burden of murder, it shook the earth to the core\nFelt like the world was collapsing. Then we heard him speak\n\"Can I still get into heaven if I kill myself?\nCan I still get into heaven if I kill myself?\nCan I ever be forgiven cuz I killed that kid?\nIt was an accident I swear it wasn\'t meant for him\nAnd if I turn it on me, if I even it out, can I still get in or will they send me to hell?\nCan I still get into heaven if I kill myself?\"\nI left the hotel behind, don\'t want to know how it ends</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_10">I heard the old man\'s voice break, stutter once then stop it\nI heard a sentence started confidently halted by the sudden absence of a word\nStumbled and he sputtered trying to find it back, something once so simple gone now\nWhen he finally gave up told me, \"Aw, it\'s like hell getting old.\"\n\nWhen you came into the store, did you know you\'d show me your scars?\n\nI had a heavy heart, he carried a door, it\'s shattered pane all wrapped in plastic and he asked if I could fix it, come by a little later help him put it back on hinges. \"See, I\'m far too old to lift it and it\'s not for my house,\nIt\'s my son\'s.\"\n\nWhen you opened up the door, what is it you thought you\'d find?\n\nNobody flinch\n\nLater I came by and backed into the driveway. Got out to find him waiting there to lead me through the side yard to back behind the house where the door frame stood empty and helped me keep it steady while I hammered all the pins in then later on the porch we somehow got to talking, he told me of the house and how is son is schizophrenic so they purchased it for him, the medication working and they figured it would help him fit in-help him lead a normal life.\n\nBut the pills made him sleep too much. And he couldn\'t keep a job as a Result so one day he just gave up on taking them.\nAnd that day she had called you, he\'d locked her outside of the house.\n\nHow quickly did you get there? And what were you thinking while walking up? What fears flashed in front of you, taunted you, walking to unlock the door?\n\nI remember it, Ed. That story you told me came back clear tonight here while writing. And you should know the feeling never left me-the weight of my heart-when you showed me the scars on your arms, when I looked in your eyes and I heard what you said how you probably would\'ve died were it not for to care for your daughter and wife. How he drove in the knife, still your son.\n\nHow you seemed to look through me to some old projector screen playing back the scene as you described it on a movie reel, as real as the minute when it happened, that memory moving behind me. That moment that changed you for good.\n\nAnd he drove to the house and pulled into the driveway. Got out to find his wife waiting, frantic. She\'d come by to check, found that pillbox was empty, went out to the pharmacy to fill up his prescription and came back to a locked door and could not get back in. She\'d knocked and she\'d knocked but he wasn\'t responding.\n\nYou put the key into the lock and turned it. Felt the bolt slide away. Slowly open. Went into the hall, his son held a knife, standing off in the shadows, lunged forward and tackled him. Stabbing him over and over and breaking that window. He fled up the staircase. The ambulance came, stitched and filled him with blood while the cops took his son with his wires so tangled his father was a stranger.\n\nAnd I sit in my apartment\nI\'m getting no answers\nI\'m finding no peace, no release from the anger\nI leave it at arms length\nI\'m keeping my distance\nFrom hotels and Jesus and blood on the carpet\nI\'m stomaching nothing\nI\'m reaching for no one\nI\'m leaving this city and I\'m headed out to nowhere\nI carry your image\nYour grandfather\'s coffin\nAnd Ed, if you hear me, I think of you often\nThat\'s all I can offer\nThat\'s all that I know how to give</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_11">Like any morning of my junior year I stumble in the classroom late but this day I see\nFaces, I feel an air like a funeral, like a wake, as I sit down\nMy teacher speaking, somewhat somberly, but still confident and calm\nPart eulogy, her speech, and part poem, part celebration song\nHer warmth and smile, she passes photocopies out to us of entries from a journal\nKept so long ago. She starts to read and suddenly it\'s 1980\n\nMarch 5\nThe cancer is furious but our son is resilient\nWe have all the faith we\'ll get through this no matter what the end\nTreatments are violent but he keeps on smiling\nIt\'s amazing finding joy in the little things\n\nApril 12\nAndrew\'s appetites improved and we thank God everyday\nBut still it\'s hard sometimes to see him in that scarecrow frame\n\nJuly 9\nThere\'s a suffering when I look in his eyes. He\'s been through so much\nWe\'ve all been through so much but what incredible resolve our little boy shows\nOnly 7, standing face to face with death\nHe said it\'s easy to find people who have suffered worse than him\n\"Like Jesus, suffered worse than anyone,\" he told me last night, \"when God abandoned him.\"\n\nSeptember 20\nWe\'ve been playing in the yard lately and spirits are high\nAlthough his blood counts aren\'t\n\nOctober 14\nHe feels tired all the time\n\nNovember 30\nAt the hospital again. It feels like home when we\'re here\n\nDecember 8\nHe\'s getting worse\n\nJanuary 19\nWe buried our son today, our youngest child\nAnd while his death was ugly we must not let it scare us from God\nAbundant grace has restored him. A brand new body\nAnd set him free from the torture, finally rid of the cancer\nBefore the moment he left he briefly wrested from death, suddenly opened his eyes, said\n\"I see everything. I see everything..\"\n\nAnd I will never forget it, the peace and the comfort you displayed through a pain\nThat I can only imagine. The loss of a child to the torture of cancer. Help me\nBecause I can only imagine how you recovered\nKept your faith and held the brightness of life inside the smile of a child you had to bury\nAnd I will never forget him or your steadfast faith\nNo, I will never forget you. Now six or seven years later, I\'m devoid of all faith\nI am empty of comfort and I am weary of waiting\nThough I\'ve felt nowhere what you have, I see nothing at all\nThough I\'ve felt nowhere what he did, my eyes are closed</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_12">So here goes\nOne last letter now. One last attempt to make sense\nWho have I been writing to? I\'m not sure anymore\nWhat have I been trying to accomplish?\nIt\'s a mystery, I guess. Self-made secrecy\nThings get cloudy and now all these stories and\nThe struggle as an undercurrent, both get blurry by the minute both get blurrier\nSo, which voice is this then that I\'ve been writing in? Is it my own or his?\nHas there ever been a difference between them at all?\n\nI don\'t know I don\'t know\n\nOne last desperate plea. One last verse to sing\nOne last laugh track to accompany the comedy\nHave I been losing it completely? Losing sanity?\nOr has it been fabricated, fashioned by the worst of me?\nI know I knocked the table over because I watched the jar break\nAnd I\'ve been trying to repair it every single stupid day\nBut won\'t the cracks still show no matter how well it\'s assembled\nCan I ever just decide to let it die and let you go?\n\nAll my motives and every single narrative below reflects\nThat moment when it broke and will I never let it go\nNo matter what? Now I am throwing all the shards away,\nDiscarding every fragment, and fumbling uncertain towards a curtain call\nThat no one wants to happen\nThat no ones going to clap for at all, but that still has to be</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_13">So now tell me how your story goes. Have you ever suffered?\nIf so, did you get better or have you never quite recovered from it?\nDid you find your lover laying in your bedroom with another and then\nDid you let it hover over you and everything else well after the fact?\n\nShow me all your bruises. I know everybody wears them\nThey broadcast the pain-how you hurt, how you reacted\nDid cancer take your child? Did your father have a heart attack?\nHave you had a moment forced the whole heart to grow or retract?\n\nOr just shrink\nDoes the heart shrink?\n\nTell me everything. Tell me everything you know\n\nWere you told as a child how cruel the whole world can be?\nDid anybody ever tell you that?\nTell me what your purpose is? Who it was that put you here and why?\nDid anybody really put you here at all?\nAnd what of those necessities? Like how to cope with tragedy and pain?\nDid anybody ever show you how?\nWhen it hits will my heart burst or break or grow strong?\nIs there really only one way to know now?\n\nI\'m not sure if I\'m ready yet to find out the hard way\nHow strong I am. What I\'m made of\nI\'m not sure if I\'m ready yet to walk through the fire\nI\'m not sure I can handle it\nDo you think if the heart keeps on shrinking\nOne day there will be no heart at all?\nAnd how long does it take?\nAm I better off just bursting or breaking?\nBecause I don\'t see my heart getting strong\n\nTell your stories to me. Show your bruises\nLet\'s see what humanity is capable of handling\n\nShe lost her kid, only seven, to cancer\nShe answered with faith in her god and carried on\nWhile he was attacked by his son and was stabbed in his stomach and his back and his arms\nHe showed me scars\n82 years old, told me, \"I still have my daughter and my wife. And I still have\nMy life and my son.\"\n\nTell me what your worst fears are. I bet they look a lot like mine\nTell me what you think about when you can\'t fall asleep at night\nTell me that you\'re struggling. Tell me that you\'re scared\nNo, tell me that you\'re terrified of life\nTell me that it\'s difficult to not think of death sometimes\nTell me how you lost. Tell me how he left. Tell me how she left\nTell me how you lost everything that you had\nTell me that it ain\'t ever coming back\nTell me about God. Tell me about love\nTell me that it\'s all of the above\nSay you think of everything in fear\nI bet you\'re not the only one does\n\nEveryone in the world comes at some point to suffering\nI wonder when I will. I wonder\nEveryone is out searching for someone or something\nI wonder what I\'ll find. I wonder</string>
    <string name="lyrics_wildlife_14">What will I find?\nSome sacred thing to help me handle the tragedy?\nOr did I once-Did I have it and lose it?\n\nNo one should ever have to walk through the fire alone\nNo one should ever have to brave that storm\nNo, everybody needs someone or something\n\nAnd when I sing, don\'t I sing your name out\nRight at the same time that I sing my own?\n\nSome days I swear I can feel you splitting the light through the window frame\nThe shapes it makes are always warmer, always brighter than the rest of what comes through\n\nSome days I swear I can hear you sing to me or whisper my name in the slightest way\nIt\'s like the warmest light now laid across my bedroom floor is somehow actually you and\nNot just sunlight\n\nI have the memory climb down the balcony\nI put a flower on the back of its dress\nIt\'s probably best to forget it\nIt\'s probably best to let go\nI paint it the shade of where the skin and the lip meet\nOnly a moment after breaking the kiss\nAnd I blur out everything else\nThat\'s how I choose to remember it\n\nSome nights are a lot like the days, I lay awake too late, I watch the shadows casted\nTrace your shape. Those silver slivers on the wall then on the bedsheets\nI hear your song in the trees. I finally fall into rest\nOften later when I\'m sleeping you show up in my dreams\nJust doing simple things, like buying groceries\nAnd when I wake up I could swear you must\'ve just left me\nLike you got up to make breakfast or maybe just to get dressed\n\nBut the truth is, you were never there. You won\'t ever be\nSometimes I think I\'m not either so what do I do\nWhen every day still seems to start and end with you?\nAnd you won\'t ever know, you won\'t ever see\nHow much your ghost since then has been defining me\n\nI leave the memory up atop the balcony\nI tear this flower from the back of the dress\nIt\'s best this time, I bet, to just forget and let go\nPaint it the shade of where the lip bleeds and blur it out\nI blur out everything else, just blur out everything else\nAnd let go, and let go, and let go\n\nEverybody has to let go someday\nEverybody has to let go\n\nI wonder when I will. I wonder\n\nBut if I still hear you singing in every city I meet\nAfter I blur it all out, our every memory, if\nYou never fade with the days, your shape still haunting me then\nShould I not just sing along?\nShould I not just sing along?\n\nI will sing sweetly hope that the notes change but\nI do not need it to happen. I\'m not resigned to it\nAnd if they never do I\'ll sing your name in every line\nJust like I did throughout this. Just like I\'ve always done\nIn every gun, the empty church, and every tortured son\nIn all those giving up. In all those giving in\nUntil I die I will sing our names in unison\n\nUntil I die I will sing our names in unison</string>

    <string name="lyrics_rooms_1">There are bridges over rivers\nThere are moments of collapse\nThere are drivers with their feet on the glass\nYou can kick but you can’t get out\nThere is history in the rooms of the house\n\nAfter dinner\nDo the dishes\nMother hums\nThe coffeemaker hisses on the stove\nThe steam a crescendo\nThe radio emergency bulletins and\nEverywhere wind\n\nYou took the train down to Terra Haute, Indiana\nVisit family, your childhood home\nGive your mother her grandkid and father a kiss\nPut your luggage in your bedroom in the kitchen sit\nWith your husband still up in Hudsonville\nUntil the weekend when his shift ends at the furniture mill\nRunning water for the dishes and the coffee on the stove\nHeard a warning from the corner on the radio\nAnd the glass starts to rattle in the window frames\n\nSo you went underground\nTook the staircase down\nTo the cellar full of hunting equipment\nHeld your baby in your arms\nRead the labels on mason jars\nTry not to think about your husband in Michigan\n\nStay calm\nKeep the radio loud\nTake care\nWind howls\nFather piles blankets in the corner by the furnace\nMother lights candles\nIt’s a miracle the baby doesn’t cry\n\nBack home doing yard work outside\nHusband being stubborn under dark skies\nSaw the fence by the neighbor’s shed split\nSaw the kitchen windows start to bend in\n\nSo you went down to the back steps then to the basement\nThere were bookshelf plans on the workbench\nAnd a flashlight shining bright all night try not to think about your son and your wife\nAnd the lightning that scattered the night sky\nAnd the wind bursts that tore up the power lines\nAt the workbench in the basement\nWhere you sat and tried to wait out the night\nYou called for three straight days\nStill with your family back home\nUp in Hudsonville the worst of the storms touched ground\nAnd the phone lines were down\nTurn the radio up\nThere’s a woman who got thrown from her car into a barbed wire fence\nShe was 6-months pregnant\nBoth her and the baby lived\nYou tried but the line or\n\nI remember those nights\nI couldn’t get through to you when quiet storms came rattled the window panes\nCouldn’t keep a thing the same way when the storm blew in and the furniture rearranged\nI can see lightning there and a funnel cloud\nAnd her mother said \"I swear I saw lightning in your eyes\nWhen that call got through to the other side.\"\n\nStay calm\nKeep the radio loud\nStay down\nThere are bridges over rivers\nSirens in the distant\nWind howls\nKeep down\nThen\nAfter dinner do the dishes\nMother hums\nWires snap\nMetal gets twisted\nThere’s the rattle of the window glass\nBending in\nTake the children down\nTerra Haute\nCoffee\nThanksgiving\nStay calm\nKeep down\nAt the workbench\nStay\nAnd the coffeemaker hisses\nStay calm\nKeep down\nTurn the radio\nThere are\nThere are moments of collapse</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_2">I knew it was far too late to walk out on the lake then\nHalfway to the middle thawed I wasn\'t doing all that great\n\nHad I cut my hair short?\nHad I grown my beard out long?\nHad I gone to school or?\n\nWhy do all my plans fall through?\n\nThere\'s a leak in the basement\nStupid permanent estrangement\nCasement windows need glazing\nHinges and arms need be replaced\n\nAll the way at the edge I said I think\nThat we should head back\nWhat if now the ice cracked?\nThink I felt it bend\n\nWe took opposite steps\nTried to even the stress\nPicked a safe direction but\nYou never know the way the ice thins\n\nHalf-asleep in dreams where\nCeilings start collapsing\nFree fall through the roof beams\nGet startled back awake\nBefore you hit the pavement\nFloor of the foundation\nWater in the basement\nBodies in the lake\n\nDon\'t panic I could hear you saying as I fell through\nBlackness complete down waiting till my feet touched ground\n\nAt the bottom they finally did\nFirst reaction was this is it\nNext thought was just stay calm kick up\nAnd save your phone\n\nBecause I wanted to tell you\nBecause I thought you should know\n\nBecause I thought it might scare you\nTo see me under the ice\nMake you remember you cared for me\nWhat would you do if I died?\nWould you fly out for my funeral?\nGet too drunk at my wake?\nWould you make a scene then?\nClimb in and try to resuscitate me?\n\nI was on the ice and I was underwater\nI was getting pulled out, I was in my wet clothes\nStumble on the walk back, someone stoked the fire at camp\nI was by the flames trying to get my body warm\nI was standing naked checking to see if my phone still worked\n\nI will cut my hair short\nTrust me, I will\nI will let my beard go\nTrust me, I will\nI will never tempt fate\nNot once, I swear\nI will never trust ice\nI will never trust a thing</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_3">Where a bookshelf goes or a throw rug\nHow you shape any common space\nAnd the language you make out of looks and names\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the weight it can hold when you say one name\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nThey grow and change\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nIn the bathroom off the kitchen\nLeave the door ajar in a brand new dress\nLet me watch put your make up on\nLet me in give me holy privileges\n\nThere\'s a dinner thing Thanksgiving\nDress up nice make a dish to bring\nThere are moments here only yours and mine\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\n\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\n\nIn the mirror with your eyes wide\nTrace outlines ask for wine\nBut you never look away when you do\nYour eyes don\'t move I never move mine from you\n\nAnd I watch you your reversal\nIt\'s an honest thing when there\'s no one there\nSome days they feel like dress rehearsals\nSome days I watch and you don\'t care\n\nThere\'s a dinner Thanksgiving\nDress up nice make a dish to bring\nThere are moments here only yours and mine\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\n\nTiny dots on an endless timeline\nGo on and on and on\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nI know, I know\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nI know, I know\n\nA glance back\nThe small of yours\nOn the sink where I set your glass\nA hand that rests there flat\nA moment\nRetracts\nAnd the recognition\nThat you give\nWhen you shift position\nMove your hip\nSlightly in\nWe say nothing then out loud and\nThat\'s what feels the most profound\n\nAnd I watched you in that apartment somewhere from across the room\nBut it\'s all a haze I remember vaguely lights then staring there to you\nIt\'s the slowest days by the bathroom that somehow never seem to go\nWhere I watched you put your make-up on\nThe smallest sounds leave the clearest echoes\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nI know, I know\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nI know, I know\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nI know, I know\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love\nI know, I know\n\nAll the motions of ordinary love</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_4">I let the car drift some\nEye your uncomfortable pose in profile\nThe postures of long drives\nThat endless cycling of your numb and near sleeping parts\n\nAnd you lean much harder than you need when the road curves\nSwerve through traffic and the cracks in the ground\nEvery gesture you require of a drive like this night\nWhen you fight now you just head out of town\n\nI let the wheel go over center lines\nInside a place without time, a loop through history\nEye you in periphery now prone in the passenger seat\nIt\'s a mystery the ways you can sleep\n\nI want to leave here for where nobody goes\nI want to breathe in the air of all those sprawling ancient spaces on earth\nYou said we\'re so scared of alone and I knew what you meant\nYou want to go where it glows all those places where your watch doesn\'t work\n\nYou were riding those nights on the highway always hiding out inside a songwriter\'s dream there\nLike a scene from a song, \"Born to Run,\" or maybe \"Running on Empty\"\nOnes where they would leave\n\nCertain nights when you\'d fight you couldn\'t stick around\nSo you\'d head out of town\nJust hit the highway and drive\nCertain nights when you\'d fight it was fine\nBut it shook you when the baby would cry\n\nWhy did you always turn around in the end?\nTo hear the shattering of glass on the door again?\nSo loud the baby couldn\'t sleep anymore?\nWhat didn\'t you find that you were looking for?\n\nYour mother called a hardware\nSet you up an interview\nAn answer to an ad\nThe bosses\' daughter still remembers dinner where her father said\nHe wouldn\'t stick his neck out for trouble again\nBut they did then\nAnd those days you\'d wake up and just decide you wouldn\'t show\nHe\'d show up at your door\nNights you\'d skip town\nHe\'d follow you out\nPretty soon you started falling for their daughter\nAnd she fell for you\n\nDrive roll every window down\nLet the desert enter heavy and primitive in\nDrift till rumble strips sound\nTime moves so slow but I know that you meant what you said\nYou want to go where it\'s frozen\nAll those places where the highways don\'t reach\n\nYou want to go where it glows\nSomewhere that time is irrelevant\nYou want to go where it glows\nSomewhere the spaces are infinite\n\nYou want to go where it glows\nSomewhere you don\'t feel the hours pass by\nYou identified the flowers on the road\nI rolled the windows down and shut off the radio\n\nDid you ever think you\'d end up here\nAll those late nights you spent driving alone?\nYou were riding to hide or you were looking for a brand new life\nDid you ever think you\'d find one back home?\n\nDid you even think you\'d get out alive?\nCould you imagine then the love you now know?\n\nI think history\'s a system of roads and there\'s nowhere it doesn\'t go\n\nI pulled over to the side and felt no time\nOff the highway with the landscape aglow\nStill not sure what we were trying to find\nI only know we went home</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_5">Funny what you think of after a collapse\nWhile lying in the dirt the first thing that comes back is never quite what you\'d have guessed\nAnd if you could have, you probably would\'ve said you\'d check if all your limbs were intact still and\nthen try to get out\n\nWe played house with the neighbors in their basement\nSister made me husband she was older so I did her bidding\nI remember once their dad came in said, \"You think this is bad?\nYou don\'t know the half.\" And he laughed\n\nIt\'s funny what things come back\nThe first things you see\n\nHow he sort of smiled like it\'s only a joke but he was lying\nThere was something else inside of his eyes\nAll those secrets people tell to little children\nAre warnings that they give them\nLike, \"Look, I\'m unhappy. Please don\'t make the same mistake as me.\"\n\nWhy are those old worn out jokes on married life told at toasts at receptions still?\nHow does it never occur how often couples get burned and end uncertain in Splitsville?\n\nFunny what you think of in the wreckage, lying there in the dirt and the dust and the glass\nHow you\'re suddenly somewhere, in the desert, in the nighttime, and it\'s getting close to Christmas\nAnd then her and that movie voice she uses when she reads\n\"Welcome to the Land of Enchantment\" from a highway sign\nAnd it\'s late so you take the next exit\n\nWhen that trip ended we came back the rent was due I was jobless\nI guess in retrospect I should\'ve sensed decay\nThen that day, how you said, \"I just don\'t know\" and I promised\nWe\'d rearrange things to fix the mess I\'d made here\n\nBut I guess in the end we just moved furniture around\nBut I guess in the end we just moved furniture around\nBut I guess in the end we just moved furniture around\n\nBut I guess in the end it sort of feels like every day it\'s harder to stay happy where you are\nThere are all these ways to look through the fence into your neighbor\'s yard\nWhy even risk it? It\'s safer to stay distant\nWhen it\'s so hard now to just be content\nBecause there\'s always something else\n\nNow I\'m proposing my own toast, composing my own joke for those married men\nMaybe I\'m miserable, I\'d rather run for mayor in Splitsville than suffer your jokes again</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_6">Drivers out on the bridge\nSlowing down as they go through a lane shift\nWires snap\nConcrete gives\nMetal twisting and\nEverything tumbling\n\nAt the end of the work day\nStuck in traffic don\'t feel when the road sways\nUnderneath\nConcrete gives\nMetal twisting and\nEverything tumbling\n\nTo their partners and kids\nDon\'t suspect anything till the bridge splits\nWires snap\nConcrete gives\nMetal twisting and\nEverything tumbling\nDown\n\nWhere I sat I saw brake lights flash\nAnd I pictured them: all the people, their faces in free fall, the water beneath\nI pushed my palms against the table hard to see if it hurt\nWere it glass would I have shattered it?\nCould I battle every impulse to panic and then win\nSwim out through the metal twisting upward like a sculpture\nOr some terrible beast?\n\nPeople trapped in their cars\nPut both feet on the glass and then kick hard\nWater pours in\nSeatbelts twist\nRiver flowing and\nEverything going down\n\nPeople under the water line\nWorkers sift through the wreckage of it find\nSeatbelts stuck\nWater fills up\nRiver flowing and\nEverything going downstream\n\nOn the dining room wall I watched it\nPlay in the reflection of the television\nThe reversal in the mirror hung I could see it all\nHow the dust clouds gather color as they billow out\nShades change shifting in the night\nFrom the lights atop an ambulance\nLike a firework\'s flash then that otherworldly glow\nIn the smoke thrown in the aftermath blows\nAlmost frozen for a moment there\nI could see it all\n\nEvery\nDust cloud\nShattered glass\nBillow out\nOn the TV\nWires snap and the\nConcrete gives\nMetal twists up and onward\nI can see it all\nEvery\nDust cloud\nShattered glass\nBillow out\nOn the TV\nWires snap and the\nConcrete gives in\nMetal twists up and onward I watch\nAnd I can see it all\n\nAll the wreckage\nAll the cars piled\nIn the river and\nThe rail yard\nMetal twists\nWires snap\nConcrete blocks split\nDangle from tie rods\nAnd metal twists up\nWires sway\nWhen a breeze blows\nIn the distant\nSirens glow\nI can see it all\nWhere they look for survivors\nSearchlights float\nChange the color of smoke clouds\nAnd shadows still fall\nPeople under the water\nPeople trapped in their cars kick and try to get out\nPeople still with their seat belts on\nPets they had in the back and\nCar seats\n\nAnd I watch it on TV lying down here\nOn the floor in the dining room reversed in the mirror\nWhere I know I\'m not dreaming now\nBut I know I\'ve been sleeping\nI just don\'t know since when\nI only know that it\'s light outside\nI only know that the rent is still late\nWhen did they find out the concrete gave?\nWhen did they learn that the wires snapped?</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_7">If I could play back every moment to you now\nSpent lovesick and swollen on\nMornings mincing garlic on the counter by the sink\nIf I could hit the instant replay on only every good day\nWould any of it catch you by surprise?\n\nWhen you say, \"something is missing now\"\nThat\'s what came back to me\nNormal mornings like that set the knife down and forget where I\'d left it\nMaking breakfast\nPut coffee on the stove then scour every counter for the knife\n\nDon\'t be shy\nDon\'t be kind\nSomewhere snow collects and bends the boughs of pines\n\nBut doesn\'t it seem a bit wasteful to you\nTo throw away all of the time we spent perfecting our love in close quarters and confines?\nIsn\'t it wasteful?\nAnd I am terrified that it doesn\'t feel painful to me yet\nSomewhere on top of the high rise there\'s a woman on the edge of a building at the ledge\nAnd traffics backing up on 35\n\nIt\'s alright\nI will fix whatever is not the sweetness in your eyes\nJust sit down\nPlease\nSit down\nHere\nAt the table and we\'ll talk\nSomewhere televisions light up in the night\n\nI know things weren\'t right\nMaybe we were never cut out for the Midwest life\nMaybe we\'d have done much better on a coast\nThere are certain things I doubt we\'ll ever know\n\nI know you were getting tired of my drinking\nI guess I was never cut out for the coke scene\nYou were worried I would end up like your father and\nTired of the smoke and somewhere the wind blows\n\nSomewhere a storm touches down north in Hudsonville\n\nSomewhere the coffee starts to boil on the stove and\nSomewhere the wind blows\n\nSomewhere the river levels finally getting low\n\nSomewhere I\'m up past dawn till\nSomewhere you live here still\nSomewhere you\'re already gone\n\nSomewhere a radio is playing in a living room\nSays the city lacks the funds to fix the bridge\n\nSomewhere the deer are overrun so they\'re introducing wolves back on the ridge\n\nAnd from here in the kitchen\nI can hear the neighbors in the alley hanging linens\nAnd the men collect the trash bins in the street\nYou\'re speaking to me but I can\'t understand you\nThe coffee is burning and\nAll of the times that we spent\nThat road trip out west\nThrough desert for the rest stops the kitsch we both collect\nThat winter the whole weekend we huddled by the stove\nThe cabin I had rented\nThe unexpected snow\nThat visit for Christmas\nOn television binges\nWe\'ll see friends in Brooklyn\nDrive south to Richmond\nThere\'s traffic on the bridge\nA woman on the ledge\nAnd everywhere the wind\n\nEverything is happening at once</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_8">There were shadows in the bedroom\nWhere the light got thrown by the lamp on the nightstand\nOn your mother\'s side, after midnight, still\nYou can see it all\nYou can see it all\nAnd the closet in the corner\nOn the far back shelf with the keepsakes, she hid\nThat box there full of letters of regret\nBy the pictures of the kids\n\nYou get faint recollections of your mother\'s sigh, countryside drive\nAnd the landscape seen from the window of the backseat with some flowers in a basket\n\nThat afternoon after school you and your older sisters\nFound your parents in the kitchen at the table\nFather lifting off the lid of the box\n\nAnd a hush fell over everything like a funeral prayer\nA reverence, ancestral, heavy in the air\n\nThough you didn\'t understand what it meant\nThat they never said her name aloud around you\nEven sitting at the table with her things they’d kept\nYou recall faintly cards, tiny clothes, and the smell of the paint in the upstairs bedroom\nUntil then you didn\'t know that’s what the box had held\n\nYour parents tiptoeing slowly around always speaking in code\n\nNo, they never said her name aloud around you\nOnly told you it was perfect where your sister went\nAnd you didn\'t understand why it hurt them so much then that she\'d come and left so soon\nCould only guess inside your head at what a \"stillbirth\" meant\nOnly knew that mother wept\n\nYou watched while father held her, said \"Some things come but can’t stay here.\"\nYou saw a brightness. Like a light through your eyes closed tight then she tumbled away.\n\nFrom here, some place\nTo remain in the nighttime shadows she made\nTo be an absence in mom, a sadness hanging over her\nLike some pentacostal flame, drifting on and off\nShe was \"Sister,\" only whispered.\nSometimes \"Her\" or\n\"The Child We Lost.\"\n\nYou were visions\nA vagueness, a faded image\nYou were visions\n\nYou were a flame lit that burned out twice as brightly as the rest of us did\nWhen you left, you were light, then you tumbled away\n\nThere are shadows that fall still here at a certain angle\nIn the bedroom on the nightstand by your mother’s side\nFrom the light left on there\n\nThere\'s the box in the closet, all the things kept\nAnd the landscape where she left\nFlowers on the grave, marble where they etched that name\nAnd mother cried the whole way home\n\nBut she never said it once out loud\nOn the way back home from where you thought they meant\nWhen they said where sister went\n\nAfter grandpa got hospice sick and he couldn\'t fall sleep\nThey wheeled his stretcher bed beside her at night\nAnd I saw the light\n\nOn the day that he died\nBy their bed in grandma\'s eyes\nWhile us grandkids said our goodbyes\n\nShe said \"don’t cry\"\nSomewhere he holds her\nSaid a name I didn\'t recognize\nAnd the light with all the shadows combined</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_9">You in the living room\nYou on a Tuesday afternoon\nA breeze seen when the curtains move\n\nYou by the window with both feet up on the couch\nWhere you sit and you read and I watch you\n\nFrom the office the sunlight frames your silhouette\nI think of lighting fireworks, I think of pirouettes\nI idly write down observations on the scene\nLike do the blueprints name the rooms alone?\nDo we name them on our own?\nWe hardly live in there\n\nYou with a book propped on your knees\nA breeze seen in your coffee steam\n\nI\'m in the office thinking back to rules of poetry\nIt\'s fourteen lines, the last two rhyme, what does pentameter mean?\n\nYou in the living room\nLegs bent at forty-five degrees\n\nI write AB AB, try to find your rhyme scheme\nI look for objects on the desk with which to sculpt your image best\nWhat would I name this could I paint it \"Woman (reading)?\" \"Girl (at rest)?\"\n\nI remember it so well watching you shifting your weight, turning the page, I can see it all there\nInside a living room where only I live and never go in\nA role in name alone\n\nAnd I pause where I am for a second when I hear your name\nSometimes I think I see your face in improbable places\nDo those moments replay for you?\nWhen I\'m suddenly there and then won\'t go away\nWhen you\'re sitting in the living room reading for the afternoon\nDo you put your book down look and try to find me there?\n\nSometimes I think of all the people who lived here before us\nHow the spaces in the memories you make change the room from just blueprints\nTo the place where you live\n\nWhen you leave here\nWhen you go from a home\nYou take all that you own but the memories echo\n\nOn hardwood floor in the living room\nTore the carpet the scratches below that we found\nAnd the wine stain on the couch\nWe got drunk and decided we\'d still try to move it around\nAnd I can\'t tell what the difference is between the ones that we made and the ones that we didn\'t make\nThey all conjure images still\nWhere you sit and you read in the sunlight aware that I watch\n\nAnd I live alone now\nSave for the echoes\n\nI live alone now\nSave for the echoes</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_10">Morning after snowstorm\nStand in the silence\nAlmost feel reborn all alone on the street\nIt\'s a certain sort of stillness when the quiet surrounds you\nThe only sound your shovel on concrete\n\nI remember those piles from the snow plows always seemed much bigger back when I was kid\nPushed all of the snow to the end of the driveway\nI was the only person up in the neighborhood\nMorning after snowstorm\n\nI turned the ignition and I started my car\nMorning after snowstorm\nI scraped off my windshield with the edge of a credit card\n\nI remember that drive into work\nStill can hear the voice coming over the radio\nListen to our experts give the best tips for the next time you entertain dinner guests\n\nI thought of the day in a tie in the kitchen I sat and I watched you put make-up on\nThought of the day in the basement when I played house\nI felt ashamed that I\'d stayed in my head in the same place for so long\nBecause I was afraid to change\nBut that\'s not an excuse to stay\n\nMorning after snowstorm\nI climbed up on the snowbank and I stared at the neighborhood\nMorning after snowstorm\nI think I finally understood what they meant when they said there\'s a calm after the storm\n\nSaw my grandpa at his workbench building grandma\'s bookshelf\nWatched a woman walk her trash out to the street\n\nFather alone on the highway\nI heard the salt trucks and neighbors off to work\nSaw my mother\nSaw how history loops around all of these moments and then I saw you\n\nIn a dress there with your eyes open wide to put make-up on\nThought of the day in the basement that I played house\nAnd I felt ashamed I\'d ignored all the hands that extended before and around me\nBecause I was afraid to change\nBut that\'s not an excuse to stay\nIt\'s not an excuse</string>
    <string name="lyrics_rooms_11">Yesterday alone I laid everything out on the carpet\nBooks, kitchen things, objects with specific purpose or none\nArranged them sideways in a grid on the floor there unmoored\nOut of context and then considered it\nFirst the whole picture, then everything individually\nHumming along at the deadest pace imaginable\nOne object then another and then the next\nAnd I wondered what they meant there\nIf they meant anything still\n\nFound notes\nCamping supplies\nA book you bought in the desert\n\"Identifying Wildflowers\"\nPictures from vacations\nFrom parties\nKitschy gifts we bought from rest stops\nOn that road trip out West\nObjects\nEverything itself\nAnd then memory\n\nAll of it laid out there\nFrom the dining room\nThe living room\nThe hallway and the basement and the kitchen\nFrom that room we called the office\nBut never used\nEven the bathroom\nEverything laid out there on the floor on the carpet out of context\n\nAnd I sat there for hours\n\nToday I moved everything from the floor to the table in the dining room\nPlaced each thing carefully without reason or at least without one I understood or could describe\nThere on the table together and when I was done and stepped back I realized what I had made\nKeepsakes Pictures Letters Ordinary objects all collected there\n\nA memorial\n\nAnd I thought of ones on highways or set by gravestones\nAll the things you see there but don\'t understand but still bring a remembered thing back vividly\nInvoke someone\'s reality when there together in that place in that way out of context\nAnd I knew I had to take it down before anybody else saw\nTomorrow I plan to put them all somewhere\nThose things\nIn boxes\nSide of the road\nAttic maybe\nAll these things that push and pull me through history\nTo places I once was, places I might\'ve gone, places I ended up going\n\nPostcards\nTicket stubs from one thing or another\nA personalized coffee mug neither your name nor mine\nPhone cards and old phones\nA page from an old calendar I bought once at a thrift store and insisted on hanging\nThat cycles of the moon print\nPhotos\nOld boots of mine\n\nPut them in boxes\n\nAnd I sat there for hours\nIn the living room first\nThen in the dining room\nMoving things around\nPicking things up and seeing where they took me\nTo what place in history\nWhat moment on our timeline\nWhere we were, where I was, where I thought we\'d end up\nIn this house or on the highway\nDriving somewhere near Christmas\nIn the desert or anywhere else\n\nAnd I put them in boxes</string>

    <string name="lyrics_untitled_1">Both butterflies and dragonflies have wings like when you sing\nI swear you hit two different notes but they don\'t harmonize as clean as\nWhen you speak there is a rhythm in the scraping of your tongue along your teeth\nThat comes across as well as hell inside of heaven in a feast of flies\nAnd anything with wings that tries to sing but where you ripped two different holes\nSee, they won\'t cauterize as cleanly as you think and if you listen to the rhythm\nIn your sleep you can hear me speaking, \"You are a wolf to me\"\n\nDon\'t believe your ears nor trust your mouth i think that\nEvery single feeble doubt-soaked promise of trust\nHad a mind to leave you\nOut in the rain with your hands to the train tracks\nPulling the ropes with your teeth\nBut you\'re too weak and\nYou\'re too tired, child, lay down\nI will tear every ghost from your dream\n\n(Oh king, you\'ve stepped on the wrong crack)\n\nRejoice!\nIt is beating still\nStill strong\nStill thundering onward\nIt turns it\'s palm up\nLifts it\'s voice up\nIt speaks, says\n\"I don\'t know.\"\n\nHe speaks with the speed in the clench of a bear trap\nSoftly rebuilding the castles he\'d kept\nSays, \"There is grace in a steeple collapsing.\"\nStraightens the sheets on the beds where they\'d slept \nThinking his love was as passive as flowers\nPlanted a garden of lies in her chest\nSays, \"There is grace in a steeple collapsing.\"\nPointing the calm in his eyes to the west to valinor\nWhere love was sent on airplane wings to shake and be shaken\n\nStill, the flowers open as she passes\nAnd the birds they sing to greet her\nThough she heaves blood\nThere is grace in a steeple collapsing\nThere is grace in a steeple collapsed\n\nAnd he said, \"Boy, get your things together\nMake them wood and make them stone and we\'ll build you a house\nThere isn\'t ever any shelter anymore.\"</string>
    <string name="lyrics_untitled_2">The lion isn\'t sacred when not sleeping near the lamb\nIt is evil when it eats unless it\'s feeding from the damned\nAll the children painted diagrams of god upon their hands\nHoping somewhere on this shaking earth they could find a place to stand\n\nIt\'s a tyrant to the foreigners who\'ve never seen the land\nThey feel safer than a statue when they\'ve got a spear in hand\nIt is pregnant with the fury that the pain in life demands\nYes, it\'s fear - but it\'s a fear that understands\n\nAnd what\'s left is a heartbeat, speaking\n\"Hands off your fate, child, you\'ll bury yourself in mistakes.\"\nLike a dream that i had of lost faith it fades away but still thunders onward\nEvery pulse was a hand with its palm up\nFed with bodies and bread soaked in blood\nSomewhere, someday, it\'ll leave but tell me, someone\nWhere does it go?\n\nWhat tied our hands tight to the train tracks, then backed off slowly?\n\nWhat does the heart say? \"See the reverse. There\'s an answer there.\"\n\nI am the moth-drenched love of dead mules\nAs stable as sand in a windstorm. and I shake like a spider in the rain\nWhen you say, \"My my, the ways I\'ve changed since then - the ways I\'ve changed.\"\nAnd all I ever say is, \"I\'m&#8230;\"\n\nAnd it hits like a brick to the back of your head\nLike, goodbye, five times, one for each finger\nAnd you say, \"My my, the ways I\'ve changed since then - the ways I\'ve changed.\"\nAnd all I ever say is, \"I\'m tired.\"\n\nWe turned our water into whining, shouting, \"Let us be like christ.\"\nBut then the whining turned to wonder, and the wonder turned to ice\nOnce, we were graceful steeples, hands held upward and eyes wide in suspense\nNow, we are tangled like intruders in the wires of the fence\n\nFor a fence is built to protect what lies inside of it\nDo you still feel sick?\nBecause I do</string>

    <string name="lyrics_herehearptone_1">In the last quarter of the twentieth century\nMuch of the world sat on the edge of an increasingly expensive theater seat\nWaiting for something momentous to occur\nChristian aficionados of the Second Coming scenario were convinced that\nAfter two thousand years, the other shoe was about to drop\nAnd five of the era\'s best-known psychics predicted\nThat Atlantis would soon re-emerge from the depths\nTo this last, Princess Leigh-Cheri responded\n\"There are three lost continents - we are one: the lovers.\"\nIn whatever esteem on might hold Princess Leigh-Cheri\'s thoughts, one must agree\nThat the last quarter of the twentieth century was a severe period for lovers\nIt was a time a time when romantic relationships took on the character of ice in spring\nStranding many little children on jagged and inhospitable floes\nNobody quite knew what to make of the moon anymore\nConsider a certain night in August\nThe moon was so bloated it was about to tip over\nFor more than an hour, Leigh-Cheri stared into the sky\n\"Does the moon have a purpose?\" She inquired\nThe same query put to the Remington SL3 elicited this response:\nAlbert Camus wrote that the only serious question\nIs whether to kill yourself or not\nTom Robbins wrote that the only serious question\nIs whether time has a beginning and an end\nCamus clearly got up on the wrong side of bed\nAnd Robbins must have forgotten to set the alarm\nThere is only one serious question. And that is:\nWho knows how to make love stay?\nAnswer me that and I will tell you whether or not to kill yourself\nAnswer me that and I will ease your mind about the beginning and end of time\nAnswer me that and I will reveal to you the purpose of the moon</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptone_2">Somewhere I have never travelled, gladly beyond\nAny experience, your eyes have their silence\nIn your most frail gesture are things which enclose me\nOr which I cannot touch because they are too near\n\nYour slightest look easily will unclose me\nThough I have closed myself as fingers\nYou open always petal by petal myself as Spring opens\nTouching skilfully, mysteriously her first rose\n\nOr if your wish be to close me, I and\nMy life will shut very beautifully, suddenly\nAs when the heart of this flower imagines\nThe snow carefully everywhere descending\n\nNothing which we are to perceive in this world equals\nThe power of your intense fragility: whose texture\nCompels me with the colour of its countries\nRendering death and forever with each breathing\n\nI do not know what it is about you that closes\nAnd opens; only something in me understands\nThe voice of your eyes is deeper than all roses\nNobody, not even the rain, has such small hands</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptone_3">It was many and many a year ago\n\nIn a kingdom by the sea\nThat a maiden there lived whom you may know\nBy the name of Annabel Lee\nAnd this maiden she lived with no other thought\nThan to love and be loved by me\n\nI was a child and she was a child\nIn that princedom by the sea\nBut we loved with a love that was\nmore than just love\nWith a love even the seraphs up in heaven covet\n\nAnd that was the reason that long ago\nIn that princedom asleep by the sea\nThat a wind shut her body in a sepulcher\nBuried in the sea\nThat bore my sweet darling away from me\n\nOh, the angels they envied us-envied our love\nYes, that was the reason the wind came out\nStirred the air and made the waves shake madly\nKilling my Annabel Lee. Oh my Annabel Lee\n\nOur love it was strong. So strong\nThat neither the angels up in heaven\nNor the demons in the sea\nCan ever dissever my soul from the\nSoul of my Annabel Lee</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptone_4">There was once a great kingdom, and its great king had a beautiful daughter who passed her days in solitude, weaving garments for the pleasure of her father. One day, while she was sitting beside the great river, peering across, she saw a handsome young shepherd boy leading his flock through the pasture. Immediately, she fell in love. Thereafter, she became terribly disheartened, knowing that, due to her duties at the loom, she would be unable to pursue that love. The king, aware that by his bidding such despair had befallen her, felt great remorse, and arranged for her to marry the shepherd.\n\nThere marriage was one of happiness from the start, and everyday thereafter they grew happier and happier. However, in immersing herself in her marriage, the princess had neglected her weaving and the great king became angry. Unable to reconcile with that anger, the great king banished each of the lovers to opposite sides of the great river, allowing them only to meet once each year: on the seventh day of the seventh month. On that day, a ferryman would carry the shepherd boy across the river to the princess, and return him home at day\'s end. However, if the princess has not fulfilled her obligations at the loom the king floods the river, and the two can not meet.</string>

    <string name="lyrics_herehearpttwo_1">Sure, I know that you are tired of hearing about it\nBut most repeat the same theme over and over again\nIt\'s as if they were trying to refine what seems so strange\nAnd off and important to them\n\nIt\'s done by everybody\nBecause each must work out what is before them over and over again\nBecause that is their personal tiny miracle\nLike now as like before\nAnd before I have been listening to symphony after symphony from this radio\nIt makes me realize that certain people now long dead\nWere able to transgress graveyards and traps and cages and bones and limbs\nIn tiny rented rooms I was struck by miracles\n\nThe flesh covers the bone and they put a mind in there\nAnd sometimes a soul and the women break vases against the walls\nAnd the men they drink too much\nAnd nobody ever finds the one\nBut keep looking crawling in and out of beds\nFlesh covers the bone and the flesh searches for more than flesh\n\nThere is a loneliness in this world \nSo great that you can see it in the slow movement of the hands of a clock\nPeople so tired, mutilated, either by love or no love\nPeople just are not good to each other\nWe are afraid\nOur educational system tells us that we can all be big winners\nBut it hasn\'t told us about the gutters or the suicides\nOr the terror of one person aching in one place\nAlone, untouched, and unspoken to\n\nPeople are not good to each other\nPeople are not good to each other\nI suppose they never will be\nI don\'t ask them to be\nBut sometimes I think about it\nThere must be a way\nSurely, there must be a way\n\nThere\'s no chance at all\nWe are all trapped by fate\nNobody ever finds the one\nNobody ever finds the one\n\nThere\'s no chance at all\nWe are all trapped by fate\nWho put this brain inside of me?\nIt says that there\'s a chance\nIt\'s kept the rope from my throat\nMaybe it will loosen yours\n\nThe city dumps fill\nThe junkyards fill\nThe graveyards fill\n\nNothing else fills\nNothing else fills\nNothing else fills</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearpttwo_2">The gods had condemned Sisyphus to ceaselessly rolling a rock to the top of a mountain\nWhence the stone would fall back of its own weight\nThey had thought with some reason \nthat there is no more dreadful punishment than futile and hopeless labor\n\nNothing is told us about Sisyphus in the underworld\nMyths are made for the imagination\nAs for this myth, one sees merely the whole effort \nof a body straining to raise the huge stone\nTo roll it and push it up a slope a hundred times over\nOne sees the face screwed up, the cheek tight against the stone\nThe wholly human security of two earth-clotted hands\nAt the very end of his long effort, the purpose is achieved\nThen Sisyphus watches the stone rush down in a few moments\nToward the lower world whence he will have to push it up again toward the summit\nHe goes back down to the plain\n\nIt is during that return, that pause, that Sisyphus interests me\nA face that toils so close to stones is already stone itself\nI see that man going back down with a heavy yet measured step\nToward the torment of which he will never know the end\nThat hour like a breathing-space which returns as surely as his suffering\nThat is the hour of consciousness\nAt each of those moments when he leaves the heights\nAnd gradually sinks toward the lairs of the gods\nHe is superior to his fate\nHe is stronger than his rock\n\nThe workman of today works everyday in his life at the same tasks\nAnd his fate is no less absurd\nBut it is tragic only at the rare moments when it becomes conscious\nSisyphus knows the whole extent of his wretched condition\nIt is what he thinks of during his descent\n\nThere is no fate that can not be surmounted by scorn\nIf the descent is thus sometimes performed in sorrow\nIt can also take place in joy\nWhen the images of earth cling too tightly to memory\nIt happens that melancholy arises in man\'s heart\nThis is the rock\'s victory\n\nBut crushing truths perish from being acknowledged\nThus, Edipus at the outset obeys fate without knowing it\nBut from the moment he knows, his tragedy begins\nYet at the same moment, he realizes that the only bond \nlinking him to the world is the cool hand of a girl\nThen a tremendous remark rings out\n\"Despite so many ordeals, my advanced age\nAnd the nobility of my soul make me conclude that all is well.\"\n\n\"I conclude that all is well,\" says Edipus\nAnd that remark is sacred\n\nIt echoes in the wild and limited universe of man\nIt teaches that all is not, has not been, exhausted\nAll Sisyphus\' silent joy is contained therein\nHis fate belongs to him\nThe rock is still rolling</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearpttwo_3">The Mole had been working very hard all the morning\nSpring-cleaning his little home\nFirst with brooms, then with dusters\nThen on ladders and steps and chairs\nWith a brush and a pail of whitewash\nTill he had dust in his throats and eyes\nAnd splashes of whitewash all over his black fur\n\nSpring was moving in the air above\nAnd in the earth below and around him\nPenetrating even his small dark and lowly little house\nWith its spirit of divine discontent and longing\nIt was small wonder, then\nThat he suddenly flung down his brush on the floor\nAnd said, \"Bother!\"\nSomething up above was calling him\n\nSo he scraped and scratched and scrabbled and scrooged\nand then scrooged again and scrabbled and scratched and scraped\nWorking busily with his little paws and muttering to himself\n\"Up we go! Up we go!\"\nUntil at last, pop\nHis snout came out into the sunlight\nAnd he found himself rolling in the warm grass of a great meadow\n\"This is fine,\" he said to himself\nAnd jumping off all his four legs at once\nIn the joy of living and the delight of spring\nHe pursued his way across the meadow\nTill he reached the hedge on the further side\n\nHither and thither through the meadows he rambled busily\nFinding everywhere birds building, flowers budding, leaves thrusting\neverything happy, and progressive, and occupied\nAnd instead of having an uneasy conscience pricking him\nHe somehow could only feel how jolly it was to be\nThe only idle dog among all these busy citizens\n\nHe thought his happiness was complete when\nAs he meandered aimlessly along\nSuddenly he stood by the edge of a full-fed river\nNever in his life had he seen a river before\nThis sleek, sinuous, full-bodied animal, chasing and chuckling\nGripping this with a gurgle and leaving them with a laugh\nTo fling itself on fresh playmates that shook themselves free\nAnd were caught and held again\nAll was a-shake and a-shiver\nFlints and gleams and sparkles, rustle and swirl, chatter and bubble\nThe mole was bewitched, entranced, fascinated\n\nBy the side of the river he trotted as on trots\nwhen very small, by the side of a man \nwho holds one spell-bound by exciting stories\nAnd when tired at last, he sat on the bank\nWhile the river chattered on to him\nA babbling procession of the best stories in the world\nSent from the heart of the earth to be told at last to the insatiable sea\n\nThe mole waggled his toes from sheer happiness\nSpread his chest with a sigh of full contentment\nAnd leaned back blissfully\n\"What a day I\'m having,\" he said</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearpttwo_4">I\'d just come out the other side of a relationship that blew up\nI was angry, and disillusioned, and ultimately self-destructive\nI\'d lost everything I believed in\nI was as utterly, completely alone as I\'ve ever been\nSo I began going on walks\n\nI started taking late-night walks around the San Diego suburb I was living in at the time\nI\'d start walking early evening, and come back close to midnight, sometimes later\nWalking and thinking and chewing over what had gone wrong with my life\n\nOne night, at Fourth and E Streets, I got mugged and beaten by a street gang\nSent me to the hospital with serious intimations of mortality\nWhen the ER techs asked what my religion was, I refused to answer\nI made my private peace with the universe\nContent with whatever was going to happen, live or die\n\nThen something happened\nI got angry\nI got angry because I still had stories to tell\nSo I fought back\n\nIt took two months to fully recover\nBut two things came out of that incident\nFirst: I have no fear of death. None whatsoever\nSecond: As soon as I was well enough, I started walking again\nSometimes until 3 or 4 in the morning\nThrough parts of town that made even street people nervous\n\nWhen people asked what I was doing out there that late at night\nthe only answer I could give was, \"I\'m looking for something.\"\nSo I kept walking through some of the most dangerous parts of San Diego\nbefore it got cleaned up\nWhen it was still home to hookers and drunks and gangs\n\nFinally, one afternoon, I came to the same areas I walked through at night\nAnd I was struck by the dichotomy between that corner at night\nAnd the very same corner during the day\nIn the daylight, there were businessmen and kids and clerks\nEager to get home to dinner and TV and family\nThen, later, came the night shift - the lost people\nemerging from shadows and beds of pain to walk the same streets\nIn search of fixes, money, and bars\nGradually fading away with the dawn\n\nTwo totally different worlds\nSharing nothing but longitude and latitude\nThere was the nation in the day, and the nation at night\nExisting side by side but each fleeing the other\nA daylight nation and a midnight nation\n\nI saw a country bifurcated by more than just the presence and absence of light\nBut by lives cast aside and lost and uncared for\nThe walked away and the thrown-away on one side, and on the other\nThose who pretended not to see them, because not seeing is easier\n\nAnd I saw someone forced to walk both sides of the metaphor\nTo learn that the greatest cruelty is our casual blindness to the despair of others\nThat there but for the grace of whatever god you subscribe to goes any of us\n\nAnd finally, I realized that I had found what I was looking for\nWithout ever being quite sure what it was\nI found a story that would make my own life make sense again\nThis story\n\nI still take long walks\nAnd I still stop and talk to the people who stand at the corner\nAnd wait for something to happen to them\nWho wait for money to fall into a hat or a cup\nWho wait for someone to recognize their pain\nBecause the line between the midnight nation\nAnd the place where I sit right now\nWriting these words, is thin and ephemeral and can be crossed in an instant\nBecause the road to the midnight nation can be erased only through compassion\n\nI found my story, this story, on a hazy afternoon in 1978\nNow it\'s yours\nThe keys to the midnight nation are in your hands\nWhat you do with them is up to you\n\nJ. Michael Straczynski\nSherman Oaks, CA\nJuly 21st, 2002</string>

    <string name="lyrics_herehearptthree_1">I recall once on the church steps\nWhen I moved to kiss your chest\nHow we paid such close attention\nTo each sweet and stuttered breath\nI should\'ve stopped to paint our picture\nCaptured honest pure affection\nJust to document the difference\nbetween attraction and connection\n\nI can see all of my friends and\nI break into empty buildings\nWhen the coast was clear\nWith backpacks full of beer\nWe\'d throw our bottles from the rooftops\nAt this city-it looked endless\nGuess I still don\'t see the difference\nbetween real purpose and that urgent adolescence\n\nAnd I remember in a basement sharing sweat\nWith all these stranger boys and girls\n\"We\'ll change the world!\"\nWe sang, \"We\'ll change the world!\"\nBut nothing seems to change and\nThey say none of them will listen\nBut I still see much more power in that basement\nThan in heartless politicians\n\nAnd if we get beaten by this winter\nIf we get strangled by regret\nJust let our love of life and tension\nGasp in sweet and stuttered breaths\nAnd have them lay us in a basement\nSmash some bottles on the ground\nAnd say we couldn't tell the difference\nBetween the feeling and the sound\n\nRemember not our faulty pieces\nRemember not our rusted parts\nIt\'s not the petty imperfections that define us but\nThe way we hold our hearts\nAnd the way we hold our heads\nI hope they write your names beside mine\nOn my gravestone when I\'m dead\nAnd when we\'re dead let our voices carry on\nTo find a better song\nTo find a better song and sing along</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptthree_2">I promised Colin I\'d keep writing\nAnd that\'s the only promise I\'ve kept\nBut I have no regrets\nLike your empty mailbox?\nIt doesn\'t bother me\nNot at all\n\nAnd I promised you I\'d come visit soon\nGuess I should\'ve made the trip\nBut money\'s tight as rope and time too\nAnd you know how it goes better than anyone\nThere isn\'t ever much of anything we need\nOr think we do\nSo I don\'t feel bad\nI don\'t feel bad\n\nAnd somewhere you cut me out\nFall in love to rinse your mouth\nBut it doesn\'t bother me at all\n\nI promised Colin I\'d take off to you soon\nOn an old deck in Louisville, KY\nFour stories up, Six AM and Ten deep\nWhile they we\'re sleeping, and I said\n\"Keep me in check, friend.\" And he tried\nBut I couldn\'t be\n\nAnd that small window closed\nAnd I never really kept writing either\nJust stared downward at the page most times\nOr thought about it real hard\nAnd there must be something missing in me\nThat she\'s there and I\'m still here because\nThat\'s messed up\nBut I don\'t feel bad about it\n\nAnd somewhere you cut me out\nFall in love to rinse your mouth\nBut it doesn\'t bother me at all\n\nI have tried hard to stay hopeful in the moments\nThey cut ropes to set you free\nI have always tried to point the finger elsewhere\nThis time it points to me\n\nBut it doesn\'t bother me at all\n\nEach chance to lock arms, to lie long in locked eyes\nAnd I failed to let go, to cut ties with my life\nBut I\'m torn, and reborn, see I died when you left\nBut each word since that day was your name from my chest\n\nI am afraid\nBut it doesn\'t bother me at all</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptthree_3">It was out on the highway\nIt was warmer than blood\nIt was spaces and basements\nFaces brimming with love\nIt was nightfall to daybreak\nFinding a new way\nIt was falling asleep at the wheel while awake\nIt was wasting away; delay the promise of heartache\nIt was tracing the chest to the arm to the hand\nThat\'s been wielding a knife and trying\nTo cut our dreams in pieces but we\'ll be fine\n\nI feel alright, tonight\nYeah, I feel alright tonight\n\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)\n\nIt was fear of foreclosure, stock in General Motors\nIt was boarding up buildings, burnt; the tortured and war-torn\nIt was unpaid rent checks and\nAll the hope left\nThe hearts that still beat through the bones in our chests\n\nI feel alright, tonight\nI guess I feel alright tonight\n\nI feel like letting go (I feel)\nI feel like letting go (Alright)\nI feel like letting go (Tonight)\nI feel like letting go, yeah\n\nI feel like giving in (I feel)\nI feel like giving in (Alright)\nI feel like giving in (Tonight)\nI feel like giving in, yeah\n\nThere\'s a chorus of voices below you\nThere\'s a prayer of hope composed in song\nIn a basement with the lights turned low and\nThere\'s room to sing along, so sing along\n\nAnd I feel alright, tonight\nYeah, I feel alright tonight\n\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)\nI feel (I feel alright)</string>
    <string name="lyrics_herehearptthree_4">Walked into find you sitting in your kitchen, softly singing\n\"Someone carry me away.\"\n\nIf there\'s always someone leaving\nWill we ever stop believing that the winter fits us perfectly?\nIsn\'t someone always coming?\nOnce the summers up and running\nWon\'t you feel warm with me?\n\nBut we\'re so tired of when we don\'t make mistakes\nBut things get torn away\nAnd we\'re so scared of losing faith\nThat we can\'t put things back together when they break\n\nWalked into find you staring out the window at a city\nHolding memories of older times and how\'d she\'d gone away\nAnd we sang through smoke and rum and coke and\nPromised with our pity, man, one day, I swear we\'ll be ok\n\nWalked into find you sitting in your kitchen, softly singing\n\"Someone carry me away.\"</string>

</resources>